<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf8"?>
<AmazonEnvelope>
  <Header>
    <DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion>
    <MerchantIdentifier>A2OI2L2OPFI67W</MerchantIdentifier>
  </Header>
  <MessageType>Product</MessageType>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>1</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521585895972-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6954520680768</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, 3 In 1 Evaporative Cooler Humidifier Purifier, 3 Speeds, 60 ° Wide Angle, Large Area Air Supply, Usb Power Supply</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to stay cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air to your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy a fresh and moist breath.<br/><br/>✔ It has three functions of lowering temperature, humidification and air purification. The wind speed can be adjusted in three speeds.<br/>✔ Silent during use, reduce temperature, environmental protection, freon-free.<br/>✔ Built-in water tank 156ML, once filled, it can last for hours.<br/>✔ USB or AC power.<br/>✔ Power: 10W.<br/>✔ Air volume: 50 CFM.<br/>✔ Power interface USB: 5V, 2A, 1A can be used.<br/>✔ Use place: office, home living room, kitchen, bedroom, bathroom and home construction area, etc.<br/>✔ Reminder: Please place the air conditioner horizontally before adding water, do not shake the machine at will.<br/><br/>✔ Cautions<br/>1. If water turns over during use, disconnect the power supply, clean the water in time, and wait for the water to dry before using it.<br/>2. Due to manual measurement and different measurement tools, there may be slight errors in the data.<br/>3. Due to different monitors, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Multiple power supply modes: three power supply modes, which can be powered by USB ports of mobile devices such as laptops. Use the charger to power from a wall outlet. When using mobile power, you don't have to worry about power failure.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Three-in-one function: three-in-one multi-functional design of purifier, air conditioner, air humidifier. Cool and humidify for better air. The cooling design keeps you away from hot summers and enjoys cool summers.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Purification and humidification: The use of plant fiber dense wet curtains, multiple fresh filters, rejects dirty air, makes the wind fresher, and breathes deeply.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Third-speed wind speed: Wide-angle air supply is cooler, third-speed wind speed can be adjusted, 60-degree wide-angle, large area of air supply is evenly distributed, and the space is cool.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Anti-pinch hand, safer: the design behind the wind, the air cooler adopts encrypted design to prevent pinch, and the safety is higher.</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
                <Color>White</Color>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>2</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521585904564-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6954520683011</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, 3 In 1 Evaporative Cooler Humidifier Purifier, Replaceable Water Curtain, Portable 3 Speed Windshield, Infinitely Variable Night Light</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to stay cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air to your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy a fresh and moist breath.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, keep away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air and enjoy a healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy efficient and low carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>Mini personal air cooler designed for personal use, please place no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Product name: Oval Water Cooling Fan<br/>✔ Water tank capacity: 380ml<br/>✔ Working current: 0.2A-1.4A<br/>✔ Input: DC5V<br/>✔ Power: 1W-7W<br/>✔ Product material: ABS / silicone<br/>✔ Wind speed: first gear: 2.36m / s, second gear: 3.24m / s, third gear: 3.94m / s<br/>✔ Noise: first gear: 30dB, second gear: 38dB, third gear: 46dB<br/>✔ Motor speed: low: 2424rpm, middle: 3337rpm, high: 3997rpm<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable<br/><br/>✔ Note:<br/>There may be slight errors in the data due to manual measurements and different measurement tools.<br/>Due to different monitors, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Night light mode: soft warm light, sleep peacefully, warm night light, enhance the mood of life and meet your sleep needs.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 3 in 1 fan: a cooling fan integrating fan, purification and cooling, humidifier integration, all functions are available.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Hand-held hanger: can be hung and hung, without any restrictions, you can experience the ubiquitous cooling anytime, anywhere. Suitable for bedroom, living room, kitchen, study, etc.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Adjustable air outlet: Manually sweep up and down to release coolness in a wide range, and enjoy a large amount of air throughout the house (do not put your fingers or foreign objects into the air outlet).</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: Our store uses international logistics, you can contact us at any time by email, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer is always the first, you can find yourself by searching for "DUYER" Favorite products, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
                <Color>White</Color>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>3</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586154759-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6111945922990</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, Cold And Warm Dual-Mode Electric Heater, Pure Humidification Without Fog, 3 Seconds Fast Heating, Small Sun Heater</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy fresh and moist breathing.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air, enjoy healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy-saving and low-carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Product name: fan heater<br/>✔ Fan heater / heater category: desktop heater<br/>✔ Color classification: coconut milk white deep space gray<br/>✔ Maximum power: less than 800W<br/>✔ Application area: less than 10㎡<br/>✔ Maximum heating area (m2): less than 20m ^ 2<br/>✔ Heater heating method: aluminum heat sink<br/>✔ Protection level: IPX2<br/>✔ Voltage: 220V ~ 50Hz<br/>✔ Water tank capacity: 400ml<br/>✔ Size: 205 * 163 * 175 mm<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x Air conditioner<br/><br/>✔ Matters needing attention:<br/>Due to manual measurements and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>Depending on the monitor, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Dual heating and cooling modes: heating in winter and air conditioning in summer, keeping the air comfortable at all times, evenly cooling at 3 seconds.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 3 speeds: high soft wind \ middle soft wind \ sleep wind, comfortable air volume can be adjusted at will, low noise and quiet without disturbing.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Mobile water tank: visual design, master water volume at any time, easy to disassemble, add water and clean. The humidifying filter can be replaced (it is recommended to replace it every six months).</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Multiple safety protection: automatic power-off when dumping, double overheat protection, anti-skid rubber pad at the bottom, multiple safety protection, safe to use.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer will always be the first, you can find yourself by searching for "DUYER" Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
                <Color>Pink</Color>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>4</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586154759-1</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6111945923003</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, Cold And Warm Dual-Mode Electric Heater, Pure Humidification Without Fog, 3 Seconds Fast Heating, Small Sun Heater</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy fresh and moist breathing.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air, enjoy healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy-saving and low-carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Product name: fan heater<br/>✔ Fan heater / heater category: desktop heater<br/>✔ Color classification: coconut milk white deep space gray<br/>✔ Maximum power: less than 800W<br/>✔ Application area: less than 10㎡<br/>✔ Maximum heating area (m2): less than 20m ^ 2<br/>✔ Heater heating method: aluminum heat sink<br/>✔ Protection level: IPX2<br/>✔ Voltage: 220V ~ 50Hz<br/>✔ Water tank capacity: 400ml<br/>✔ Size: 205 * 163 * 175 mm<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x Air conditioner<br/><br/>✔ Matters needing attention:<br/>Due to manual measurements and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>Depending on the monitor, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Dual heating and cooling modes: heating in winter and air conditioning in summer, keeping the air comfortable at all times, evenly cooling at 3 seconds.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 3 speeds: high soft wind \ middle soft wind \ sleep wind, comfortable air volume can be adjusted at will, low noise and quiet without disturbing.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Mobile water tank: visual design, master water volume at any time, easy to disassemble, add water and clean. The humidifying filter can be replaced (it is recommended to replace it every six months).</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Multiple safety protection: automatic power-off when dumping, double overheat protection, anti-skid rubber pad at the bottom, multiple safety protection, safe to use.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer will always be the first, you can find yourself by searching for "DUYER" Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
                <Color>White</Color>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>5</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586157016-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6111945922921</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, Refrigeration Mini Usb Fan Humidifier, Foldable Storage, Spray Cooling, Arbitrary Adjustment Of Wind Direction</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy fresh and moist breathing.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air, enjoy healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy-saving and low-carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>The mini personal air cooler specially designed for personal use should be placed no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Product name: Folding humidifier fan<br/>✔ Voltage input: DC5V<br/>✔ Working current: 500-1500mA<br/>✔ Battery capacity: 2000mAh<br/>✔ Water tank volume: 300mL<br/>✔ Product size: 115x11 5x135mm<br/>✔ Product weight: 377G<br/>✔ Product color: green<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x Air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable<br/><br/>✔ Matters needing attention:<br/>Due to manual measurements and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>Depending on the monitor, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Atomization technology: Atomization technology of water molecules is used to allow water molecules to fully diffuse into the air so as not to cause water droplets to flow back and wet the desktop, effectively reducing the surrounding temperature.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Simple design: clean and pure, the fan can be folded and stored, and it can be folded when not in use. It is a landscape when you put it away. Two buttons control the air supply and spray buttons separately, clear and easy to use, let you enjoy the comfort and coolness.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ The third gear wind is soft and soft: the third gear wind is adjustable, one-key control, single press to turn on the fan and enter the weak gear, press twice the middle gear, press 3 times the strong gear, and finally turn off the fan.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 180 ° free wind direction: You can adjust the air supply angle. Air supply at different angles is convenient for your daily life. You can also fold and store the fan when it is not in use. It is simple and fun to use.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer will always be the first, you can find yourself by searching for "DUYER" Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
                <Color>Green</Color>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>6</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586159996-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6111945922747</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, 4 In 1 Multifunctional Air Cooler, Usb Household Refrigeration Spray Humidifier, Office In Bed In Student Dormitory</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy fresh and moist breathing.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air, enjoy healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy-saving and low-carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>The mini personal air cooler specially designed for personal use should be placed no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Product name: mini air cooler<br/>✔ Product color: white<br/>✔ Product weight: 1kg<br/>✔ Product size: 156 * 145 * 230mm<br/>✔ Water tank volume: about 700M<br/>✔ Material: ABS environmental protection plastic<br/>✔ Rated input: DC 5V<br/>✔ Maximum power: about 7.5W<br/>✔ Battery capacity: about 5000mAh<br/>✔ Fan gear position: third gear wind speed<br/>✔ Refrigeration gear: third gear refrigeration<br/><br/>The package includes:<br/>1 x Air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 4-in-1 air conditioner: 4-in-1 air cooler, humidifier, air conditioner, water replenishment meter, small fan, multi-function fan, small size, large energy.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Wide-angle shaking his head and blowing hair: 60 ° and 120 ° two kinds of shaking his head, so you don't have to worry about the problem of not blowing, and you can cool and cover everything. Large volume of 300ml / h fog, spread fog and spread far.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 6 gear adjustments: 3 gears for blowing and 3 gears for spraying, a variety of gear adjustments to meet different temperature requirements, ABS environmentally friendly materials, ice and water on top, bottom hose to guide water.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Quiet companionship: The new brushless high-speed motor not only improves the running speed, but also has a very good performance in terms of noise. You can enjoy comfortable air even during sleep.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer will always be the first, you can find yourself by searching for "DUYER" Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
                <Color>White</Color>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>7</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586163537-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6111945922594</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, Air Cooler Humidifier, Ultraviolet Disinfection Rate 99%, 4 In 1 Mini Usb Air Conditioner, Suitable For Home Office</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy fresh and moist breathing.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air, enjoy healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy-saving and low-carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>The mini personal air cooler specially designed for personal use should be placed no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Net weight: 1200g<br/>✔ Input voltage: 5V<br/>✔ Cooling power: 2.5-3w<br/>✔ Capacity: 500ml<br/>✔ Size: 16 * 14.4 * 20.6cm<br/>✔ Cooling range: 5-10 ℃<br/><br/>✔ The package includes:<br/>Air-cooled humidifier x 1<br/>Manual x 1]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 99% bacteria elimination: UV germicidal lamp has two main spectral lines, namely 254nm and 185nm. 254 Nm ultraviolet rays kill bacteria by irradiating microbial DNA. 185nm ultraviolet can convert O2 in the air to O3 (ozone). Ozone has a strong oxidation effect and can effectively kill bacteria. Dispersibility of ozone.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Multi-function desktop radiator: multi-function fan with humidification function / cooling function / air purification function / Bluetooth function. Atomizing fan, fan with humidification function.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 7-color lamp cooler: There are 7 colors to choose from, so you can choose a color you like to create a romantic atmosphere.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Portable cooling fan: compact, easy to carry and easy to store. Small size, with handle design. Small size, light weight and easy to carry. Can be used in offices, bedrooms, and homes.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer is always the first, you can find yourself by searching for "DUYER" Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
                <Color>White</Color>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>8</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586165236-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6111945922532</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, 7-Color Led Light, Evaporative Humidifier 3-Speed Cooling Fan, Home, Office</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy fresh and moist breathing.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air, enjoy healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy-saving and low-carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>The mini personal air cooler specially designed for personal use should be placed no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Power mode: USB<br/>✔ Rated voltage: 12v | 24v<br/>✔ Rated power: 8w<br/>✔ Applicable area: office, bedroom, home<br/>✔ Noise: below 36db<br/>✔ Wind speed gear: third gear<br/>✔ Speed ​​control gear: third gear<br/>✔ Water tank capacity: 375ml<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x Air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Multi-function and LED light: This portable air cooler has three functions, including air cooling, humidification and purification. It can also display 7-color LED lights to bring more fun to users.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Portable handle: portable design, small size, you can easily take it anywhere, very suitable for home, office, outdoor picnic, etc., and the USB input makes it work anywhere via USB power (power / USB plug).</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Quick cooling: Quickly cool the hot air around you. With 3 fan speeds, you can choose the ideal wind power according to your needs. This air private space regulator allows you to add ice or ice water to the tank to speed up the cooling rate.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Energy saving-low energy consumption: same as the energy consumption of light bulbs, without using Freon, it is much cheaper than running Freon air conditioner in hot summer. No blade will expose any possibility of harm to people, and can be safely used by children or pets.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer is always the first, you can find yourself by searching for "DUYER" Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
                <Color>White</Color>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>9</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586225656-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6111945926721</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Portable Air Cooler, Mini Air Conditioner, Three Levels Of Wind Power, Fan Purification And Cooling Humidifier Integrated Cooler, Silent Spray Large Wind Power Cold</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy fresh and moist breathing.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air, enjoy healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy-saving and low-carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>The mini personal air cooler specially designed for personal use should be placed no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Material: ABS / PP / electronic components<br/>✔ Weight: 830g<br/>✔ Battery voltage: 3.7V<br/>✔ Battery capacity: 2000mAh<br/>✔ Input voltage / current: DC5V / 1A<br/>✔ Output power: 4W<br/>✔ Fan working current: first gear 240mA / second gear 460mA / third gear 730mA<br/>✔ Negative ion working voltage / current: 1W<br/>✔ Ion concentration: 1X10PCS / cm3<br/>✔ Ozone concentration: &lt;0.03PPm<br/>✔ Product size: 190X152X 160mm<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x Air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ USB charging cooler: built-in 2000 mAh large-capacity battery, no matter where you are, can meet your needs, cool anytime, anywhere, lasting cooling, comfortable home.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Fan button: 1. Click the fan button to turn the fan on and off. Click on the first gear of the fan for the first time (lower gear by default). Click on the second gear for the second time, and click on the third gear for the third time. 2. Long press the fan button to start the intermittent blowing mode, blow for 10 seconds and stop for 10 seconds, click again to switch the continuous blowing mode</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Indicator function: the blue light is always on when blowing continuously; the blue light flashes when in gust mode, the green light is on when the negative ions are working, the red light is always on when charging, and the red light is off when the battery is full, and the green light flashes when the power is low.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Can be carried by the handle: can be carried and hung, unlimited placement, compact and does not occupy space, portable handle, convenient and labor-saving, random experience at any time to cool everywhere.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer is always the first, you can find yourself by searching for &amp;quot;DUYER&amp;quot; Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
                <Color>Pink</Color>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>10</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586225656-1</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6111945926738</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Portable Air Cooler, Mini Air Conditioner, Three Levels Of Wind Power, Fan Purification And Cooling Humidifier Integrated Cooler, Silent Spray Large Wind Power Cold</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy fresh and moist breathing.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air, enjoy healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy-saving and low-carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>The mini personal air cooler specially designed for personal use should be placed no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Material: ABS / PP / electronic components<br/>✔ Weight: 830g<br/>✔ Battery voltage: 3.7V<br/>✔ Battery capacity: 2000mAh<br/>✔ Input voltage / current: DC5V / 1A<br/>✔ Output power: 4W<br/>✔ Fan working current: first gear 240mA / second gear 460mA / third gear 730mA<br/>✔ Negative ion working voltage / current: 1W<br/>✔ Ion concentration: 1X10PCS / cm3<br/>✔ Ozone concentration: &lt;0.03PPm<br/>✔ Product size: 190X152X 160mm<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x Air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ USB charging cooler: built-in 2000 mAh large-capacity battery, no matter where you are, can meet your needs, cool anytime, anywhere, lasting cooling, comfortable home.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Fan button: 1. Click the fan button to turn the fan on and off. Click on the first gear of the fan for the first time (lower gear by default). Click on the second gear for the second time, and click on the third gear for the third time. 2. Long press the fan button to start the intermittent blowing mode, blow for 10 seconds and stop for 10 seconds, click again to switch the continuous blowing mode</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Indicator function: the blue light is always on when blowing continuously; the blue light flashes when in gust mode, the green light is on when the negative ions are working, the red light is always on when charging, and the red light is off when the battery is full, and the green light flashes when the power is low.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Can be carried by the handle: can be carried and hung, unlimited placement, compact and does not occupy space, portable handle, convenient and labor-saving, random experience at any time to cool everywhere.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer is always the first, you can find yourself by searching for &amp;quot;DUYER&amp;quot; Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
                <Color>Blue</Color>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>11</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586225656-2</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6111945926745</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Portable Air Cooler, Mini Air Conditioner, Three Levels Of Wind Power, Fan Purification And Cooling Humidifier Integrated Cooler, Silent Spray Large Wind Power Cold</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy fresh and moist breathing.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air, enjoy healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy-saving and low-carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>The mini personal air cooler specially designed for personal use should be placed no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Material: ABS / PP / electronic components<br/>✔ Weight: 830g<br/>✔ Battery voltage: 3.7V<br/>✔ Battery capacity: 2000mAh<br/>✔ Input voltage / current: DC5V / 1A<br/>✔ Output power: 4W<br/>✔ Fan working current: first gear 240mA / second gear 460mA / third gear 730mA<br/>✔ Negative ion working voltage / current: 1W<br/>✔ Ion concentration: 1X10PCS / cm3<br/>✔ Ozone concentration: &lt;0.03PPm<br/>✔ Product size: 190X152X 160mm<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x Air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ USB charging cooler: built-in 2000 mAh large-capacity battery, no matter where you are, can meet your needs, cool anytime, anywhere, lasting cooling, comfortable home.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Fan button: 1. Click the fan button to turn the fan on and off. Click on the first gear of the fan for the first time (lower gear by default). Click on the second gear for the second time, and click on the third gear for the third time. 2. Long press the fan button to start the intermittent blowing mode, blow for 10 seconds and stop for 10 seconds, click again to switch the continuous blowing mode</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Indicator function: the blue light is always on when blowing continuously; the blue light flashes when in gust mode, the green light is on when the negative ions are working, the red light is always on when charging, and the red light is off when the battery is full, and the green light flashes when the power is low.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Can be carried by the handle: can be carried and hung, unlimited placement, compact and does not occupy space, portable handle, convenient and labor-saving, random experience at any time to cool everywhere.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer is always the first, you can find yourself by searching for &amp;quot;DUYER&amp;quot; Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
                <Color>White</Color>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>12</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586245859-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>3895554857548</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Portable Air Cooler, Mini Air Conditioner, Desktop Small Air Conditioner Usb Air-Conditioning Fan, Fast Cooling, Humidifying And Replenishing Water</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy fresh and moist breathing.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air, enjoy healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy-saving and low-carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>The mini personal air cooler specially designed for personal use should be placed no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x Air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable<br/><br/>✔ Matters needing attention:<br/>Due to manual measurements and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>Depending on the monitor, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Rapid Icy: The fiber ice curtain is powerfully cooled. The high-temperature air passes the fiber ice curtain to achieve strong refrigeration. The cooling speed is fast, and the ice is cool.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Filtration and purification: dual technology healthy cool wind, high-density dust-proof filter ice curtain, purification system, like the refreshing wind after rain, as if you are in the forest.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Freely adjust the speed: 1--100 files of humanized stepless speed regulation, 100-speed adjustable wind speed, freely blow your favorite feeling to meet your different needs.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 1000ML large capacity: detachable water tank, 1000ML large capacity detachable design, eliminating the trouble of frequent water addition, making cooling more convenient and intimate.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer will always be the first, you can find yourself by searching for &amp;quot;DUYER&amp;quot; Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
                <Color>White</Color>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>13</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586246529-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>3895554858477</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Portable Air Cooler, Mini Air Conditioner, Temperature Display Multi-Function Air Conditioner, Spray Refrigeration Air Conditioner, 350Ml Large Water Tank</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy fresh and moist breathing.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air, enjoy healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy-saving and low-carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>The mini personal air cooler specially designed for personal use should be placed no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ For problems<br/>The weather is hot, the fan can only flow air when blowing, and when the temperature is too high, the blowing is hot and cannot be cooled.<br/>✔ Solution<br/>On the basis of air blowing, use the water tank to soak the ice curtain. After the ice curtain is wet, the temperature inside the body cools down, and the wind blows out is cool wind.<br/>✔ Achieve the effect<br/>Cool down first, then blow, the cool wind blows out.<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x Air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 350ml large water tank: uncover the water injection design, top the water tank, remove the cover and add water. Ice water can be added to the water tank. The lower the water temperature, the more obvious the cooling effect.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ High wind power in the DC air duct: The DC frame has smooth wind output, and the DC air duct reduces turbulent consumption of the airflow, making the airflow flow smoothly, with low noise and high wind power.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Three gear wind adjustment: gear display, digital screen display, three gear wind speed adjustment, sleep, office, home use in multiple scenarios. The gear button and LED display on the forehead are beautiful and elegant.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Upgrade 7 feather leaves: evenly cut the wind for comfortable wind output, decode the natural wind flow, and use the upgraded 7 feather leaves design.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer will always be the first, you can find yourself by searching for &amp;quot;DUYER&amp;quot; Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
                <Color>White</Color>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>14</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586247254-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>3895554858491</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Portable Air Cooler, Mini Air Conditioner, 7 Color Lights Adjustable, 3 Speeds, Office Cooling And Cooling, Small Purifier Humidifier</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy fresh and moist breathing.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air, enjoy healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy-saving and low-carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>The mini personal air cooler specially designed for personal use should be placed no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x Air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable<br/><br/>✔ Matters needing attention:<br/>Due to manual measurements and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>Depending on the monitor, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Three in one function: personal air conditioning cooler, fan, air humidifier three in one multifunctional design. Cool, humidify to get better air, and the cooling design keeps you away from the hot summer and enjoy the cool summer.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Multiple power supply methods: three power supply methods, you can use the USB port of mobile devices such as laptop computers to supply power. Use the charger to power the wall outlet. When using a mobile power supply, there is no need to worry about power failure.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 7-color lamp cooler: The light of the product is available in 7 colors, so you can choose a color you like to create a romantic atmosphere. Don't worry about black, it will give you a sense of security even if you wake up at night.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Wide range of uses: small size, small footprint, easy to carry and move, and USB type, so it can be used not only in offices, bedrooms, homes, but also outdoors, in cars or camping.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer is always the first, you can find yourself by searching for &amp;quot;DUYER&amp;quot; Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
                <Color>White</Color>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>15</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586248653-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>3895554859979</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Portable Air Cooler, Mini Air Conditioner, Handle Portable Usb Small Refrigeration Cooling, 12 Hours Timer, Home Dormitory Students</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy fresh and moist breathing.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air, enjoy healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy-saving and low-carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>The mini personal air cooler specially designed for personal use should be placed no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Product name: portable cooler<br/>✔ Air volume gear: 2 gears<br/>✔ USB cable: 1.2 meters<br/>✔ Power requirements: DC5V, 1 ~ 2.0A<br/>✔ Sink capacity: 500ML<br/>✔ Net weight: 700g<br/>✔ Product size: 178 * 125 * 200mm<br/>✔ Product gross weight: 0.875KG (single) with packaging<br/>✔ Packing size: 182 * 129 * 206mm (single)<br/>✔ Filter element: wood pulp paper<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x Air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Large capacity water tank cooling: 500ML capacity water tank, USB direct power supply or AC current power supply, 120CM USB charger cable.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Timer function: 12 hours timer, long time fixed time function, no longer worry about getting cold at night</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Soft wind mute: ABS plastic, lightweight is not a motive force, natural wind, gentle and stable wind, is your good partner.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 3-in-1 function: rapid cooling system, wind speed can be adjusted in two gears for cooling, humidification and air purification.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer will always be the first, you can find yourself by searching for &amp;quot;DUYER&amp;quot; Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
                <Color>White</Color>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>16</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586251035-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>3895554860074</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Portable Air Cooler, Mini Air Conditioner, Colorful Double Night Lights, Thimble Zero Pressure Water Tank Design, Usb Air Conditioning Humidifier Cooler, Home Dormitory Office</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy fresh and moist breathing.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air, enjoy healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy-saving and low-carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>The mini personal air cooler specially designed for personal use should be placed no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Product name: desktop cooling fan<br/>✔ Input voltage: 5V<br/>✔ Output power: 5W<br/>✔ Net weight of product: 0.8KG<br/>✔ Water tank capacity: 700ml<br/>✔ Product size: 160 * 155 * 165mm<br/>✔ Power cord length: about 1 meter<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x Air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Colorful lamp cooler: The light of the product is available in 7 colors, so you can choose a color you like to create a romantic atmosphere. Don't worry about black, it will give you a sense of security even if you wake up at night.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Portable cooling fan: compact, easy to carry and easy to store. This atomized cold air fan is 8 inches tall and compact, so it can be easily carried without taking up space.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Thimble zero-pressure water tank design: quantitative water will not overflow, bid farewell to the traditional embedded integrated water tank, using a new generation of fully sealed thimble zero-pressure independent water tank, to avoid overflow leakage.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ New-generation filter element: It gives you a more three-dimensional cooling and humidification. It is made of PVC material. It has a long-lasting bubble without odor and no deterioration. It can be brushed and can be used for a long time. Replace the filter element within 6 months.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer is always the first, you can find yourself by searching for &amp;quot;DUYER&amp;quot; Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
                <Color>White</Color>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>17</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586252445-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>3895554860432</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, Table Lamp Fan 2-In-1 Small Air Conditioner, Usb Double 7-Blade Fan, Environmental Protection, Safety And Energy-Saving Cooler</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy fresh and moist breathing.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air, enjoy healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy-saving and low-carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>The mini personal air cooler specially designed for personal use should be placed no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Product specifications:<br/>✔ Product name: air cooler<br/>✔ Rated voltage: DC5V 1A<br/>✔ Power supply method: USB<br/>✔ Rated power: 5W<br/>✔ Product size: 185 * 100 * 88mm<br/>✔ Power cord length: about 1 meter<br/>✔ Cooling method: triangle ice crystal<br/>✔ Color selection: silver<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x Air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable<br/><br/>✔ Matters needing attention:<br/>Due to manual measurements and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>Depending on the monitor, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Energy saving and health: The small air circulator does not contain ozone refrigerant. It can protect the health of your family. This mini air conditioner saves space and is economical. In summer, it is an ideal gift for you, your family and friends.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Easy to use and portable: all you have to do is add water and ice cubes to the water tank of this desktop air cooler, plug it into a USB port or power bank, and then turn it on. Mini height, easy to move, perfect for your desktop and office / dormitory.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ USB interface: Notebook, computer host, charging head, charging treasure, car, etc., as long as there is a USB power supply interface, you can use it quickly.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Adjustable air outlet: It is designed with up and down adjustable air outlet, the air is wider and the air volume is larger. The power cord is about 1 meter long, convenient and fast.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer is always the first, you can find yourself by searching for &amp;quot;DUYER&amp;quot; Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
                <Color>White</Color>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>18</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586252511-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>9859476757045</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, 3-Stage Adjustable Desktop Fan, 360 ° Rotating Cooler, And Dual-Turbo Technology For Various Scenarios</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>The mini personal air cooler specially designed for personal use should be placed no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Product parameters:<br/>Product Name: Desktop Fan<br/>Air volume gear: three gears<br/>Fan material: ABS material<br/>Voltage power: 220V- 50Hz 30W<br/>Product weight: 1.05kg<br/>Product size: 19 * 15 * 15cm<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x Air conditioner<br/>1 x charging cable<br/><br/>✔ Matters needing attention:<br/>Due to manual measurements and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>Depending on the monitor, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Multifunctional: personal air conditioner cooler, fan, multifunctional design. Cooling, blowing to get better air, cooling design keeps you away from the hot summer and enjoy the cool summer.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Three kinds of wind speed: Three kinds of wind speed (high, medium and low) 360 degrees freely adjust the wind direction to create your own personal cooling area. You can choose the most suitable one to enjoy your leisure time, sleep or work time.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Wide range of uses: small size, small footprint, easy to carry and move, can be used in offices, bedrooms, and homes, and can easily cope with various scenarios.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Twin-turbine bladeless fan: the kinetic energy is converted into pressure energy through the scroll casing, and the new gas is sucked into the impeller gas under the action of the pressure difference and is continuously discharged from the wind, and the temperature is evenly cooled in a large area at various angles.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer is always the first, you can find yourself by searching for &amp;quot;DUYER&amp;quot; Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
                <Color>Brown</Color>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>19</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521585895972</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6954520679977</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, 3 In 1 Evaporative Cooler Humidifier Purifier, 3 Speeds, 60 ° Wide Angle, Large Area Air Supply, Usb Power Supply</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to stay cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air to your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy a fresh and moist breath.<br/><br/>✔ It has three functions of lowering temperature, humidification and air purification. The wind speed can be adjusted in three speeds.<br/>✔ Silent during use, reduce temperature, environmental protection, freon-free.<br/>✔ Built-in water tank 156ML, once filled, it can last for hours.<br/>✔ USB or AC power.<br/>✔ Power: 10W.<br/>✔ Air volume: 50 CFM.<br/>✔ Power interface USB: 5V, 2A, 1A can be used.<br/>✔ Use place: office, home living room, kitchen, bedroom, bathroom and home construction area, etc.<br/>✔ Reminder: Please place the air conditioner horizontally before adding water, do not shake the machine at will.<br/><br/>✔ Cautions<br/>1. If water turns over during use, disconnect the power supply, clean the water in time, and wait for the water to dry before using it.<br/>2. Due to manual measurement and different measurement tools, there may be slight errors in the data.<br/>3. Due to different monitors, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Multiple power supply modes: three power supply modes, which can be powered by USB ports of mobile devices such as laptops. Use the charger to power from a wall outlet. When using mobile power, you don't have to worry about power failure.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Three-in-one function: three-in-one multi-functional design of purifier, air conditioner, air humidifier. Cool and humidify for better air. The cooling design keeps you away from hot summers and enjoys cool summers.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Purification and humidification: The use of plant fiber dense wet curtains, multiple fresh filters, rejects dirty air, makes the wind fresher, and breathes deeply.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Third-speed wind speed: Wide-angle air supply is cooler, third-speed wind speed can be adjusted, 60-degree wide-angle, large area of air supply is evenly distributed, and the space is cool.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Anti-pinch hand, safer: the design behind the wind, the air cooler adopts encrypted design to prevent pinch, and the safety is higher.</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>20</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521585904564</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6954520682403</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, 3 In 1 Evaporative Cooler Humidifier Purifier, Replaceable Water Curtain, Portable 3 Speed Windshield, Infinitely Variable Night Light</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to stay cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air to your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy a fresh and moist breath.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, keep away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air and enjoy a healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy efficient and low carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>Mini personal air cooler designed for personal use, please place no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Product name: Oval Water Cooling Fan<br/>✔ Water tank capacity: 380ml<br/>✔ Working current: 0.2A-1.4A<br/>✔ Input: DC5V<br/>✔ Power: 1W-7W<br/>✔ Product material: ABS / silicone<br/>✔ Wind speed: first gear: 2.36m / s, second gear: 3.24m / s, third gear: 3.94m / s<br/>✔ Noise: first gear: 30dB, second gear: 38dB, third gear: 46dB<br/>✔ Motor speed: low: 2424rpm, middle: 3337rpm, high: 3997rpm<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable<br/><br/>✔ Note:<br/>There may be slight errors in the data due to manual measurements and different measurement tools.<br/>Due to different monitors, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Night light mode: soft warm light, sleep peacefully, warm night light, enhance the mood of life and meet your sleep needs.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 3 in 1 fan: a cooling fan integrating fan, purification and cooling, humidifier integration, all functions are available.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Hand-held hanger: can be hung and hung, without any restrictions, you can experience the ubiquitous cooling anytime, anywhere. Suitable for bedroom, living room, kitchen, study, etc.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Adjustable air outlet: Manually sweep up and down to release coolness in a wide range, and enjoy a large amount of air throughout the house (do not put your fingers or foreign objects into the air outlet).</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: Our store uses international logistics, you can contact us at any time by email, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer is always the first, you can find yourself by searching for "DUYER" Favorite products, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>21</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586154759</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6111945922983</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, Cold And Warm Dual-Mode Electric Heater, Pure Humidification Without Fog, 3 Seconds Fast Heating, Small Sun Heater</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy fresh and moist breathing.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air, enjoy healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy-saving and low-carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Product name: fan heater<br/>✔ Fan heater / heater category: desktop heater<br/>✔ Color classification: coconut milk white deep space gray<br/>✔ Maximum power: less than 800W<br/>✔ Application area: less than 10㎡<br/>✔ Maximum heating area (m2): less than 20m ^ 2<br/>✔ Heater heating method: aluminum heat sink<br/>✔ Protection level: IPX2<br/>✔ Voltage: 220V ~ 50Hz<br/>✔ Water tank capacity: 400ml<br/>✔ Size: 205 * 163 * 175 mm<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x Air conditioner<br/><br/>✔ Matters needing attention:<br/>Due to manual measurements and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>Depending on the monitor, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Dual heating and cooling modes: heating in winter and air conditioning in summer, keeping the air comfortable at all times, evenly cooling at 3 seconds.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 3 speeds: high soft wind \ middle soft wind \ sleep wind, comfortable air volume can be adjusted at will, low noise and quiet without disturbing.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Mobile water tank: visual design, master water volume at any time, easy to disassemble, add water and clean. The humidifying filter can be replaced (it is recommended to replace it every six months).</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Multiple safety protection: automatic power-off when dumping, double overheat protection, anti-skid rubber pad at the bottom, multiple safety protection, safe to use.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer will always be the first, you can find yourself by searching for "DUYER" Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>22</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586157016</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6111945922914</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, Refrigeration Mini Usb Fan Humidifier, Foldable Storage, Spray Cooling, Arbitrary Adjustment Of Wind Direction</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy fresh and moist breathing.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air, enjoy healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy-saving and low-carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>The mini personal air cooler specially designed for personal use should be placed no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Product name: Folding humidifier fan<br/>✔ Voltage input: DC5V<br/>✔ Working current: 500-1500mA<br/>✔ Battery capacity: 2000mAh<br/>✔ Water tank volume: 300mL<br/>✔ Product size: 115x11 5x135mm<br/>✔ Product weight: 377G<br/>✔ Product color: green<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x Air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable<br/><br/>✔ Matters needing attention:<br/>Due to manual measurements and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>Depending on the monitor, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Atomization technology: Atomization technology of water molecules is used to allow water molecules to fully diffuse into the air so as not to cause water droplets to flow back and wet the desktop, effectively reducing the surrounding temperature.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Simple design: clean and pure, the fan can be folded and stored, and it can be folded when not in use. It is a landscape when you put it away. Two buttons control the air supply and spray buttons separately, clear and easy to use, let you enjoy the comfort and coolness.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ The third gear wind is soft and soft: the third gear wind is adjustable, one-key control, single press to turn on the fan and enter the weak gear, press twice the middle gear, press 3 times the strong gear, and finally turn off the fan.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 180 ° free wind direction: You can adjust the air supply angle. Air supply at different angles is convenient for your daily life. You can also fold and store the fan when it is not in use. It is simple and fun to use.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer will always be the first, you can find yourself by searching for "DUYER" Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>23</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586159996</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6111945922730</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, 4 In 1 Multifunctional Air Cooler, Usb Household Refrigeration Spray Humidifier, Office In Bed In Student Dormitory</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy fresh and moist breathing.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air, enjoy healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy-saving and low-carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>The mini personal air cooler specially designed for personal use should be placed no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Product name: mini air cooler<br/>✔ Product color: white<br/>✔ Product weight: 1kg<br/>✔ Product size: 156 * 145 * 230mm<br/>✔ Water tank volume: about 700M<br/>✔ Material: ABS environmental protection plastic<br/>✔ Rated input: DC 5V<br/>✔ Maximum power: about 7.5W<br/>✔ Battery capacity: about 5000mAh<br/>✔ Fan gear position: third gear wind speed<br/>✔ Refrigeration gear: third gear refrigeration<br/><br/>The package includes:<br/>1 x Air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 4-in-1 air conditioner: 4-in-1 air cooler, humidifier, air conditioner, water replenishment meter, small fan, multi-function fan, small size, large energy.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Wide-angle shaking his head and blowing hair: 60 ° and 120 ° two kinds of shaking his head, so you don't have to worry about the problem of not blowing, and you can cool and cover everything. Large volume of 300ml / h fog, spread fog and spread far.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 6 gear adjustments: 3 gears for blowing and 3 gears for spraying, a variety of gear adjustments to meet different temperature requirements, ABS environmentally friendly materials, ice and water on top, bottom hose to guide water.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Quiet companionship: The new brushless high-speed motor not only improves the running speed, but also has a very good performance in terms of noise. You can enjoy comfortable air even during sleep.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer will always be the first, you can find yourself by searching for "DUYER" Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>24</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586163537</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6111945922587</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, Air Cooler Humidifier, Ultraviolet Disinfection Rate 99%, 4 In 1 Mini Usb Air Conditioner, Suitable For Home Office</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy fresh and moist breathing.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air, enjoy healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy-saving and low-carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>The mini personal air cooler specially designed for personal use should be placed no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Net weight: 1200g<br/>✔ Input voltage: 5V<br/>✔ Cooling power: 2.5-3w<br/>✔ Capacity: 500ml<br/>✔ Size: 16 * 14.4 * 20.6cm<br/>✔ Cooling range: 5-10 ℃<br/><br/>✔ The package includes:<br/>Air-cooled humidifier x 1<br/>Manual x 1]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 99% bacteria elimination: UV germicidal lamp has two main spectral lines, namely 254nm and 185nm. 254 Nm ultraviolet rays kill bacteria by irradiating microbial DNA. 185nm ultraviolet can convert O2 in the air to O3 (ozone). Ozone has a strong oxidation effect and can effectively kill bacteria. Dispersibility of ozone.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Multi-function desktop radiator: multi-function fan with humidification function / cooling function / air purification function / Bluetooth function. Atomizing fan, fan with humidification function.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 7-color lamp cooler: There are 7 colors to choose from, so you can choose a color you like to create a romantic atmosphere.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Portable cooling fan: compact, easy to carry and easy to store. Small size, with handle design. Small size, light weight and easy to carry. Can be used in offices, bedrooms, and homes.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer is always the first, you can find yourself by searching for "DUYER" Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>25</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586165236</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6111945922525</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, 7-Color Led Light, Evaporative Humidifier 3-Speed Cooling Fan, Home, Office</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy fresh and moist breathing.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air, enjoy healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy-saving and low-carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>The mini personal air cooler specially designed for personal use should be placed no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Power mode: USB<br/>✔ Rated voltage: 12v | 24v<br/>✔ Rated power: 8w<br/>✔ Applicable area: office, bedroom, home<br/>✔ Noise: below 36db<br/>✔ Wind speed gear: third gear<br/>✔ Speed ​​control gear: third gear<br/>✔ Water tank capacity: 375ml<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x Air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Multi-function and LED light: This portable air cooler has three functions, including air cooling, humidification and purification. It can also display 7-color LED lights to bring more fun to users.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Portable handle: portable design, small size, you can easily take it anywhere, very suitable for home, office, outdoor picnic, etc., and the USB input makes it work anywhere via USB power (power / USB plug).</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Quick cooling: Quickly cool the hot air around you. With 3 fan speeds, you can choose the ideal wind power according to your needs. This air private space regulator allows you to add ice or ice water to the tank to speed up the cooling rate.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Energy saving-low energy consumption: same as the energy consumption of light bulbs, without using Freon, it is much cheaper than running Freon air conditioner in hot summer. No blade will expose any possibility of harm to people, and can be safely used by children or pets.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer is always the first, you can find yourself by searching for "DUYER" Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>26</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586225656</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6111945926707</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Portable Air Cooler, Mini Air Conditioner, Three Levels Of Wind Power, Fan Purification And Cooling Humidifier Integrated Cooler, Silent Spray Large Wind Power Cold</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy fresh and moist breathing.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air, enjoy healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy-saving and low-carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>The mini personal air cooler specially designed for personal use should be placed no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Material: ABS / PP / electronic components<br/>✔ Weight: 830g<br/>✔ Battery voltage: 3.7V<br/>✔ Battery capacity: 2000mAh<br/>✔ Input voltage / current: DC5V / 1A<br/>✔ Output power: 4W<br/>✔ Fan working current: first gear 240mA / second gear 460mA / third gear 730mA<br/>✔ Negative ion working voltage / current: 1W<br/>✔ Ion concentration: 1X10PCS / cm3<br/>✔ Ozone concentration: &lt;0.03PPm<br/>✔ Product size: 190X152X 160mm<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x Air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ USB charging cooler: built-in 2000 mAh large-capacity battery, no matter where you are, can meet your needs, cool anytime, anywhere, lasting cooling, comfortable home.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Fan button: 1. Click the fan button to turn the fan on and off. Click on the first gear of the fan for the first time (lower gear by default). Click on the second gear for the second time, and click on the third gear for the third time. 2. Long press the fan button to start the intermittent blowing mode, blow for 10 seconds and stop for 10 seconds, click again to switch the continuous blowing mode</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Indicator function: the blue light is always on when blowing continuously; the blue light flashes when in gust mode, the green light is on when the negative ions are working, the red light is always on when charging, and the red light is off when the battery is full, and the green light flashes when the power is low.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Can be carried by the handle: can be carried and hung, unlimited placement, compact and does not occupy space, portable handle, convenient and labor-saving, random experience at any time to cool everywhere.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer is always the first, you can find yourself by searching for &amp;quot;DUYER&amp;quot; Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>27</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586245859</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>3895554857517</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Portable Air Cooler, Mini Air Conditioner, Desktop Small Air Conditioner Usb Air-Conditioning Fan, Fast Cooling, Humidifying And Replenishing Water</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy fresh and moist breathing.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air, enjoy healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy-saving and low-carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>The mini personal air cooler specially designed for personal use should be placed no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x Air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable<br/><br/>✔ Matters needing attention:<br/>Due to manual measurements and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>Depending on the monitor, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Rapid Icy: The fiber ice curtain is powerfully cooled. The high-temperature air passes the fiber ice curtain to achieve strong refrigeration. The cooling speed is fast, and the ice is cool.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Filtration and purification: dual technology healthy cool wind, high-density dust-proof filter ice curtain, purification system, like the refreshing wind after rain, as if you are in the forest.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Freely adjust the speed: 1--100 files of humanized stepless speed regulation, 100-speed adjustable wind speed, freely blow your favorite feeling to meet your different needs.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 1000ML large capacity: detachable water tank, 1000ML large capacity detachable design, eliminating the trouble of frequent water addition, making cooling more convenient and intimate.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer will always be the first, you can find yourself by searching for &amp;quot;DUYER&amp;quot; Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>28</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586246529</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>3895554857715</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Portable Air Cooler, Mini Air Conditioner, Temperature Display Multi-Function Air Conditioner, Spray Refrigeration Air Conditioner, 350Ml Large Water Tank</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy fresh and moist breathing.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air, enjoy healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy-saving and low-carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>The mini personal air cooler specially designed for personal use should be placed no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ For problems<br/>The weather is hot, the fan can only flow air when blowing, and when the temperature is too high, the blowing is hot and cannot be cooled.<br/>✔ Solution<br/>On the basis of air blowing, use the water tank to soak the ice curtain. After the ice curtain is wet, the temperature inside the body cools down, and the wind blows out is cool wind.<br/>✔ Achieve the effect<br/>Cool down first, then blow, the cool wind blows out.<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x Air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 350ml large water tank: uncover the water injection design, top the water tank, remove the cover and add water. Ice water can be added to the water tank. The lower the water temperature, the more obvious the cooling effect.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ High wind power in the DC air duct: The DC frame has smooth wind output, and the DC air duct reduces turbulent consumption of the airflow, making the airflow flow smoothly, with low noise and high wind power.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Three gear wind adjustment: gear display, digital screen display, three gear wind speed adjustment, sleep, office, home use in multiple scenarios. The gear button and LED display on the forehead are beautiful and elegant.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Upgrade 7 feather leaves: evenly cut the wind for comfortable wind output, decode the natural wind flow, and use the upgraded 7 feather leaves design.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer will always be the first, you can find yourself by searching for &amp;quot;DUYER&amp;quot; Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>29</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586247254</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>3895554858484</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Portable Air Cooler, Mini Air Conditioner, 7 Color Lights Adjustable, 3 Speeds, Office Cooling And Cooling, Small Purifier Humidifier</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy fresh and moist breathing.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air, enjoy healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy-saving and low-carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>The mini personal air cooler specially designed for personal use should be placed no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x Air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable<br/><br/>✔ Matters needing attention:<br/>Due to manual measurements and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>Depending on the monitor, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Three in one function: personal air conditioning cooler, fan, air humidifier three in one multifunctional design. Cool, humidify to get better air, and the cooling design keeps you away from the hot summer and enjoy the cool summer.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Multiple power supply methods: three power supply methods, you can use the USB port of mobile devices such as laptop computers to supply power. Use the charger to power the wall outlet. When using a mobile power supply, there is no need to worry about power failure.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 7-color lamp cooler: The light of the product is available in 7 colors, so you can choose a color you like to create a romantic atmosphere. Don't worry about black, it will give you a sense of security even if you wake up at night.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Wide range of uses: small size, small footprint, easy to carry and move, and USB type, so it can be used not only in offices, bedrooms, homes, but also outdoors, in cars or camping.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer is always the first, you can find yourself by searching for &amp;quot;DUYER&amp;quot; Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>30</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586248653</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>3895554859955</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Portable Air Cooler, Mini Air Conditioner, Handle Portable Usb Small Refrigeration Cooling, 12 Hours Timer, Home Dormitory Students</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy fresh and moist breathing.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air, enjoy healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy-saving and low-carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>The mini personal air cooler specially designed for personal use should be placed no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Product name: portable cooler<br/>✔ Air volume gear: 2 gears<br/>✔ USB cable: 1.2 meters<br/>✔ Power requirements: DC5V, 1 ~ 2.0A<br/>✔ Sink capacity: 500ML<br/>✔ Net weight: 700g<br/>✔ Product size: 178 * 125 * 200mm<br/>✔ Product gross weight: 0.875KG (single) with packaging<br/>✔ Packing size: 182 * 129 * 206mm (single)<br/>✔ Filter element: wood pulp paper<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x Air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Large capacity water tank cooling: 500ML capacity water tank, USB direct power supply or AC current power supply, 120CM USB charger cable.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Timer function: 12 hours timer, long time fixed time function, no longer worry about getting cold at night</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Soft wind mute: ABS plastic, lightweight is not a motive force, natural wind, gentle and stable wind, is your good partner.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 3-in-1 function: rapid cooling system, wind speed can be adjusted in two gears for cooling, humidification and air purification.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer will always be the first, you can find yourself by searching for &amp;quot;DUYER&amp;quot; Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>31</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586251035</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>3895554860050</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Portable Air Cooler, Mini Air Conditioner, Colorful Double Night Lights, Thimble Zero Pressure Water Tank Design, Usb Air Conditioning Humidifier Cooler, Home Dormitory Office</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy fresh and moist breathing.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air, enjoy healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy-saving and low-carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>The mini personal air cooler specially designed for personal use should be placed no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Product name: desktop cooling fan<br/>✔ Input voltage: 5V<br/>✔ Output power: 5W<br/>✔ Net weight of product: 0.8KG<br/>✔ Water tank capacity: 700ml<br/>✔ Product size: 160 * 155 * 165mm<br/>✔ Power cord length: about 1 meter<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x Air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Colorful lamp cooler: The light of the product is available in 7 colors, so you can choose a color you like to create a romantic atmosphere. Don't worry about black, it will give you a sense of security even if you wake up at night.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Portable cooling fan: compact, easy to carry and easy to store. This atomized cold air fan is 8 inches tall and compact, so it can be easily carried without taking up space.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Thimble zero-pressure water tank design: quantitative water will not overflow, bid farewell to the traditional embedded integrated water tank, using a new generation of fully sealed thimble zero-pressure independent water tank, to avoid overflow leakage.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ New-generation filter element: It gives you a more three-dimensional cooling and humidification. It is made of PVC material. It has a long-lasting bubble without odor and no deterioration. It can be brushed and can be used for a long time. Replace the filter element within 6 months.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer is always the first, you can find yourself by searching for &amp;quot;DUYER&amp;quot; Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>32</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586252445</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>3895554860098</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, Table Lamp Fan 2-In-1 Small Air Conditioner, Usb Double 7-Blade Fan, Environmental Protection, Safety And Energy-Saving Cooler</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy fresh and moist breathing.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air, enjoy healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy-saving and low-carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>The mini personal air cooler specially designed for personal use should be placed no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Product specifications:<br/>✔ Product name: air cooler<br/>✔ Rated voltage: DC5V 1A<br/>✔ Power supply method: USB<br/>✔ Rated power: 5W<br/>✔ Product size: 185 * 100 * 88mm<br/>✔ Power cord length: about 1 meter<br/>✔ Cooling method: triangle ice crystal<br/>✔ Color selection: silver<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x Air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable<br/><br/>✔ Matters needing attention:<br/>Due to manual measurements and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>Depending on the monitor, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Energy saving and health: The small air circulator does not contain ozone refrigerant. It can protect the health of your family. This mini air conditioner saves space and is economical. In summer, it is an ideal gift for you, your family and friends.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Easy to use and portable: all you have to do is add water and ice cubes to the water tank of this desktop air cooler, plug it into a USB port or power bank, and then turn it on. Mini height, easy to move, perfect for your desktop and office / dormitory.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ USB interface: Notebook, computer host, charging head, charging treasure, car, etc., as long as there is a USB power supply interface, you can use it quickly.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Adjustable air outlet: It is designed with up and down adjustable air outlet, the air is wider and the air volume is larger. The power cord is about 1 meter long, convenient and fast.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer is always the first, you can find yourself by searching for &amp;quot;DUYER&amp;quot; Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>33</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521586252511</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>3895554860104</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, 3-Stage Adjustable Desktop Fan, 360 ° Rotating Cooler, And Dual-Turbo Technology For Various Scenarios</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to keep cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air on your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>The mini personal air cooler specially designed for personal use should be placed no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Product parameters:<br/>Product Name: Desktop Fan<br/>Air volume gear: three gears<br/>Fan material: ABS material<br/>Voltage power: 220V- 50Hz 30W<br/>Product weight: 1.05kg<br/>Product size: 19 * 15 * 15cm<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x Air conditioner<br/>1 x charging cable<br/><br/>✔ Matters needing attention:<br/>Due to manual measurements and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>Depending on the monitor, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Multifunctional: personal air conditioner cooler, fan, multifunctional design. Cooling, blowing to get better air, cooling design keeps you away from the hot summer and enjoy the cool summer.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Three kinds of wind speed: Three kinds of wind speed (high, medium and low) 360 degrees freely adjust the wind direction to create your own personal cooling area. You can choose the most suitable one to enjoy your leisure time, sleep or work time.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Wide range of uses: small size, small footprint, easy to carry and move, can be used in offices, bedrooms, and homes, and can easily cope with various scenarios.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Twin-turbine bladeless fan: the kinetic energy is converted into pressure energy through the scroll casing, and the new gas is sucked into the impeller gas under the action of the pressure difference and is continuously discharged from the wind, and the temperature is evenly cooled in a large area at various angles.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: our store uses international logistics, you can contact us by email at any time, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer is always the first, you can find yourself by searching for &amp;quot;DUYER&amp;quot; Like the product, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>portable air conditioner mini air cooler Evaporative Coolers air conditioning unit humidifier fans for bedroom Mobile Air Conditioners Evaporative Coolers Split-System Wall Window quiet desktop usb air conditioner handheld compact small dehumidifier 12000 btu</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
</AmazonEnvelope>
