<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf8"?>
<AmazonEnvelope>
  <Header>
    <DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion>
    <MerchantIdentifier>A2OI2L2OPFI67W</MerchantIdentifier>
  </Header>
  <MessageType>Product</MessageType>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>1</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521585816247-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6954520667721</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, 4 In 1 Anion Air Conditioner Fan Humidifier Air Purifier Air Conditioner, Usb Powered Led Night Light</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ Desea mantenerse fresco en el caluroso verano, pero le preocupa que le cueste mucho hacer funcionar el aire acondicionado todo el día, y los ventiladores comunes solo le darán aire caliente en la cara.<br/><br/>✔ ¿Quieres una mejor manera de calmarte?<br/>Use nuestro mini enfriador de aire para obtener este enfriador de espacio personal para crear su zona de confort. Simplemente agregue agua y hielo al tanque de agua, luego relájese y disfrute de un aliento fresco y húmedo.<br/><br/>✔ Ventilador de enfriamiento y humidificador<br/>El aire acondicionado, el enfriador de aire evaporativo portátil y el humidificador atomizador se combinan en uno, lo que puede humedecer la piel y el aire, mantenerse alejado del aire seco y disfrutar del frescor del verano.<br/><br/>✔ Aire fresco y disfruta de una vida saludable<br/>Reduce la temperatura por evaporación del agua y produce aire fresco. ¡Bajo consumo de energía y largo tiempo de humidificación! Es energéticamente eficiente y baja en carbono.<br/><br/>✔ Nombre del producto: aire acondicionado de escritorio pequeño<br/>✔ material: ABS<br/>✔ Peso: 700G<br/>✔ Corriente: 300mA<br/>✔ Número de tiendas: 24 juegos / cartón<br/>✔ Estado activado: 1.er viento + 1.a luz de la noche (no se pueden encender dos niveles al mismo tiempo)<br/>✔ Se puede agregar agua: se puede agregar agua natural, agua helada<br/>✔ Tamaño: 171MM * 150MM * 151MM<br/><br/>✔ El paquete incluye:<br/>1 x aire acondicionado<br/>1 x cable de datos USB]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Four-in-one multifunction: An air cooler with night lights, cooling, humidification and air purification functions allows you to create a personal comfort zone.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Take it with you, fast cooling: You only need to add water and ice in the water tank to quickly cool down. A water tank (150 ml) filled with water can run for up to 8 hours. You can take it with you and use it conveniently.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Top water filling, easy filling: Open top water filling design, simple and beautiful, easy and convenient when adding water.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Easy to use: The air cooler with USB power is more convenient to move and the noise is as low as 36db.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: Our store uses international logistics, you can contact us at any time by email, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer is always the first, you can find yourself by searching for "DUYER" Favorite products, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>desk fan usb quiet mini cooling battery handheld portable rechargeable turbo lcd touch screen, 3-speed mode easy to operate retro design 4inch bedroom office living room speeds turbofan 35w energy saving powered with led</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
                <Color>White</Color>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>2</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521585817648-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6954520668247</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, Mini Air-Conditioning Fan, 3 Speeds Fast Cooling, Bedroom Dormitory Office Humidifier</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to stay cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air to your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy a fresh and moist breath.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, keep away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air and enjoy a healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy efficient and low carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Low-noise air-conditioning: Does it use low-noise DC fans to stir the surrounding air with a large suction force? Very easy to carry to the office, bedroom, living room, kitchen and outdoors.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Large-scale air output: 90 ° wide-angle air outlet, 3 seconds of super-fast wind power, powerful air supply, cool air.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 3 speed adjustment: Our mini air conditioner is designed with 3 speed modes, which can be freely adjusted according to your requirements (low / medium / high). Sweep wind up and down, automatic adjustment. (Note: Portable air coolers are not suitable for cooling the entire room.)</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Easy to operate and lightweight: Just add water or ice water, then plug the USB cable into a mobile power supply or any USB interface, and you can use the portable mini air cooler by pressing the function button. This personal air conditioner has a mini-portable design with a retractable handle on the top of the air cooler and is only 7.2 inches high.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: Our store uses international logistics, you can contact us at any time by email, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer is always the first, you can find yourself by searching for "DUYER" Favorite products, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>desk fan usb quiet mini cooling battery handheld portable rechargeable turbo lcd touch screen, 3-speed mode easy to operate retro design 4inch bedroom office living room speeds turbofan 35w energy saving powered with led</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
                <Color>Black</Color>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>3</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521585819007-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6954520668308</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, 3 In 1 Water Cooling Fan, Simple Humanized Design, Multiple Wind Options, Removable Water Tank</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to stay cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air to your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy a fresh and moist breath.<br/><br/>✔ Material: ABS + PP + PC + Silicon<br/>✔ Product size: 170 * 152 * 157mm<br/>✔ Water tank capacity: 380ml<br/>✔ Water use time: about 3-8 hours<br/>✔ Wind speed: level 3<br/>✔ Unit weight: 850g<br/>✔ Input voltage: DC 5V<br/>✔ Color: White<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Versatile functions and LED lights: This portable air cooler has three functions including air cooling, humidification and purification. Unlike other air conditioners, this USB fan can maintain indoor humidity without making your skin feel dry. It can also display warm LED lights at night.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint> ✔ Portable and easy to use: The portable USB air cooler is compact, portable and easily moved. You can put it in the kitchen, dormitory and office or wherever you like. In addition, you can take it with you when you are outdoors in the hot summer.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint> ✔ Fast cooling: This personal air cooler can quickly cool the hot air around you. With 3 fan speeds, you can choose the ideal wind force according to your needs. With this personal desktop fan, you can add ice or ice water to the water tank for faster cooling.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint> ✔ Energy saving and environmental protection: The evaporative air cooler and humidifier are Freon-free air conditioners, which can reduce energy consumption. It is supported by the USB port and can run for a long time after being filled with water. You can use this mini air cooler safely all night long because it is very environmentally friendly.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint> ✔ Ultra-quiet operation: This portable fan can work powerfully at low noise levels. In full operating mode, the quality of air cooling remains unaffected. This ultra-quiet air cooler allows you to sleep comfortably all night, with the right temperature and low noise.</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>desk fan usb quiet mini cooling battery handheld portable rechargeable turbo lcd touch screen, 3-speed mode easy to operate retro design 4inch bedroom office living room speeds turbofan 35w energy saving powered with led</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
                <Color>White</Color>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>4</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521585820217-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6954520668322</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, 4-In-1 Humidifier Cooler, 3-Speed Desktop Cooling Fan, Suitable For Home, Room, Office</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to stay cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air to your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy a fresh and moist breath.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, keep away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air and enjoy a healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy efficient and low carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>Mini personal air cooler designed for personal use, please place no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 4-in-1 design: This evaporative air cooler has portable fan cooling, spray humidification, air purification and 4-in-1 functions of 7 LED lights, which not only reduces the temperature, but also helps us avoid dry air. In addition, it has a 7-color LED ambient light, and a soft and colorful LED light built in to create a romantic atmosphere and provide you with a better sleeping environment.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 3 speed adjustment: Our mini air conditioner is designed with 3 speed modes, which can be freely adjusted according to your requirements (low / medium / high). If necessary, you can also adjust the wind direction to rotate vertically. (Note: Portable air coolers are not suitable for cooling the entire room.)</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Energy saving and health: This portable air cooler has low energy consumption and is freon-free. Not only does it protect the health of your family, it also consumes only 3.5 watts of power to minimize energy loss and protect the environment. Ideal for summer living room, bedroom, office, etc. cooling. Can also be used at work and travel.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Easy to operate and lightweight: Just add water or ice water, then plug the USB cable into a mobile power supply or any USB interface, and you can use the portable mini air cooler by pressing the function button.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: Our store uses international logistics, you can contact us at any time by email, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer is always the first, you can find yourself by searching for "DUYER" Favorite products, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>desk fan usb quiet mini cooling battery handheld portable rechargeable turbo lcd touch screen, 3-speed mode easy to operate retro design 4inch bedroom office living room speeds turbofan 35w energy saving powered with led</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
                <Color>White</Color>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>5</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521585821092-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6954520668346</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, Desktop Mini Air Conditioner Fan, Usb Cooling And Water Cooler Desktop Humidifier Fan, Office, Bedroom, Living Room, Kitchen And Outdoor</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to stay cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air to your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy a fresh and moist breath.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, keep away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air and enjoy a healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy efficient and low carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Name: Desktop Cooler<br/>✔ Color: White<br/>✔ Material: ABS<br/>✔ Negative ion concentration: 3 million / cm3<br/>✔ Input voltage: 5V<br/>✔ Ozone concentration: <0.05PPM<br/>✔ Input current: 1.5-2A<br/>✔ Rated power: 5W<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Double protection of deep humidification: In addition to normal evaporative humidification, active atomization can be turned on</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>Yes, it can strengthen the humidifying effect to cope with the severe and hot summer.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Easy to operate and lightweight: Just add water or ice water, then plug the USB cable into a mobile power supply or any USB interface, and you can use the portable mini air cooler by pressing the function button.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Portable design: This personal air conditioner uses a mini-portable design, with a retractable handle on the top of the air cooler, which is only 7.2 inches high. It is very easy to carry to the office, bedroom, living room, kitchen and outdoor.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Energy saving and health: This portable air cooler has low energy consumption and is freon-free. It not only protects the health of your family, but also minimizes energy loss and protects the environment. Can also be used at work and travel.</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>desk fan usb quiet mini cooling battery handheld portable rechargeable turbo lcd touch screen, 3-speed mode easy to operate retro design 4inch bedroom office living room speeds turbofan 35w energy saving powered with led</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
                <Color>White</Color>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>6</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521585822622-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6954520668360</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Portable Air Cooler, Mini Air Conditioner, Touch Control 3 Speed Fan Speed, Usb Powered, For Home Office Outdoor</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to stay cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air to your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy a fresh and moist breath.<br/><br/>✔ Product name: USB Mini Cooler<br/>✔ Material: ABS material<br/>✔ Product size: 140 * 155 * 175mm<br/>✔ Power: 5W<br/>✔ Working voltage: 1A<br/>✔ Input voltage: 5V<br/>✔ Size: 170 * 170 * 205mm<br/><br/>✔ Packing list<br/>1 * Cooler<br/>1 * USB cable<br/>1 * Manual (Chinese and English)]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ With three functions of cooling, humidification and air purification, the wind speed can be adjusted in three speeds;</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Quiet use, free of freon in environmental protection and refrigeration;</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Built-in 160ml water tank, once filled, can last 8 hours;</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ USB charging or AC power supply; USB cable length: 85cm</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Use place: office, home living room, kitchen, bedroom, bathroom and home construction area, etc.</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>desk fan usb quiet mini cooling battery handheld portable rechargeable turbo lcd touch screen, 3-speed mode easy to operate retro design 4inch bedroom office living room speeds turbofan 35w energy saving powered with led</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
                <Color>White</Color>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>7</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521585823584-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6954520668384</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, 3-Speed Wind Speed, Liftable Handle Design, Usb Power Supply For Multiple Scenes, Office Desk, Dormitory Bedroom</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to stay cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air to your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add it to the water tank, then relax and enjoy a fresh and moist breath.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air and enjoy a healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy efficient and low carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>Mini personal air cooler designed for personal use, please place no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Product name: Personal Ice Fan<br/>✔ Net weight: 650G<br/>✔ Blowing range: 40-60CM<br/>✔ Volume: 460ML<br/>✔ Working current: 500MA<br/>✔ Interface: 5V2A MICRO USB interface<br/>✔ Cooling power: 150-300W<br/>✔ Size: 13.1 * 13.1 * 17CM<br/>✔ Cooling range: 3-10 ° C (the actual temperature depends on the humidity and temperature of the use environment)<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable<br/>1 x instruction manual<br/><br/>✔ Note:<br/>There may be slight errors in the data due to manual measurements and different measurement tools.<br/>Due to different monitors, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 3-speed wind speed: personal ice fan, light wind speed: suitable for meditation sitting to drive out summer impetuousness; stroke speed: suitable for desks and tables; strong wind speed: suitable for sweltering dormitories, dissipating--heat.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Versatile: Small size, small footprint, easy to carry and move, and USB type, so it can be used not only in the office, bedroom, or home.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Energy saving and health: Small air circulator does not contain ozone refrigerant. It can protect the health of your family. This mini air conditioner is both space saving and economical. In the summer, it is the ideal gift for you, your family and friends.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Multiple power supply methods: three power supply methods, you can use the USB port of mobile devices such as laptop computers to supply power. Use the charger to power from a wall outlet. When using mobile power, you don't have to worry about power failure.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: Our store uses international logistics, you can contact us at any time by email, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer is always the first, you can find yourself by searching for "DUYER" Favorite products, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>desk fan usb quiet mini cooling battery handheld portable rechargeable turbo lcd touch screen, 3-speed mode easy to operate retro design 4inch bedroom office living room speeds turbofan 35w energy saving powered with led</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
                <Color>Black</Color>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>8</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521585816247</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6954520667707</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, 4 In 1 Anion Air Conditioner Fan Humidifier Air Purifier Air Conditioner, Usb Powered Led Night Light</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ Desea mantenerse fresco en el caluroso verano, pero le preocupa que le cueste mucho hacer funcionar el aire acondicionado todo el día, y los ventiladores comunes solo le darán aire caliente en la cara.<br/><br/>✔ ¿Quieres una mejor manera de calmarte?<br/>Use nuestro mini enfriador de aire para obtener este enfriador de espacio personal para crear su zona de confort. Simplemente agregue agua y hielo al tanque de agua, luego relájese y disfrute de un aliento fresco y húmedo.<br/><br/>✔ Ventilador de enfriamiento y humidificador<br/>El aire acondicionado, el enfriador de aire evaporativo portátil y el humidificador atomizador se combinan en uno, lo que puede humedecer la piel y el aire, mantenerse alejado del aire seco y disfrutar del frescor del verano.<br/><br/>✔ Aire fresco y disfruta de una vida saludable<br/>Reduce la temperatura por evaporación del agua y produce aire fresco. ¡Bajo consumo de energía y largo tiempo de humidificación! Es energéticamente eficiente y baja en carbono.<br/><br/>✔ Nombre del producto: aire acondicionado de escritorio pequeño<br/>✔ material: ABS<br/>✔ Peso: 700G<br/>✔ Corriente: 300mA<br/>✔ Número de tiendas: 24 juegos / cartón<br/>✔ Estado activado: 1.er viento + 1.a luz de la noche (no se pueden encender dos niveles al mismo tiempo)<br/>✔ Se puede agregar agua: se puede agregar agua natural, agua helada<br/>✔ Tamaño: 171MM * 150MM * 151MM<br/><br/>✔ El paquete incluye:<br/>1 x aire acondicionado<br/>1 x cable de datos USB]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Four-in-one multifunction: An air cooler with night lights, cooling, humidification and air purification functions allows you to create a personal comfort zone.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Take it with you, fast cooling: You only need to add water and ice in the water tank to quickly cool down. A water tank (150 ml) filled with water can run for up to 8 hours. You can take it with you and use it conveniently.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Top water filling, easy filling: Open top water filling design, simple and beautiful, easy and convenient when adding water.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Easy to use: The air cooler with USB power is more convenient to move and the noise is as low as 36db.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: Our store uses international logistics, you can contact us at any time by email, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer is always the first, you can find yourself by searching for "DUYER" Favorite products, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>desk fan usb quiet mini cooling battery handheld portable rechargeable turbo lcd touch screen, 3-speed mode easy to operate retro design 4inch bedroom office living room speeds turbofan 35w energy saving powered with led</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>9</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521585817648</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6954520668216</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, Mini Air-Conditioning Fan, 3 Speeds Fast Cooling, Bedroom Dormitory Office Humidifier</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to stay cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air to your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy a fresh and moist breath.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, keep away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air and enjoy a healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy efficient and low carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Low-noise air-conditioning: Does it use low-noise DC fans to stir the surrounding air with a large suction force? Very easy to carry to the office, bedroom, living room, kitchen and outdoors.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Large-scale air output: 90 ° wide-angle air outlet, 3 seconds of super-fast wind power, powerful air supply, cool air.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 3 speed adjustment: Our mini air conditioner is designed with 3 speed modes, which can be freely adjusted according to your requirements (low / medium / high). Sweep wind up and down, automatic adjustment. (Note: Portable air coolers are not suitable for cooling the entire room.)</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Easy to operate and lightweight: Just add water or ice water, then plug the USB cable into a mobile power supply or any USB interface, and you can use the portable mini air cooler by pressing the function button. This personal air conditioner has a mini-portable design with a retractable handle on the top of the air cooler and is only 7.2 inches high.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: Our store uses international logistics, you can contact us at any time by email, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer is always the first, you can find yourself by searching for "DUYER" Favorite products, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>desk fan usb quiet mini cooling battery handheld portable rechargeable turbo lcd touch screen, 3-speed mode easy to operate retro design 4inch bedroom office living room speeds turbofan 35w energy saving powered with led</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>10</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521585819007</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6954520668292</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, 3 In 1 Water Cooling Fan, Simple Humanized Design, Multiple Wind Options, Removable Water Tank</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to stay cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air to your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy a fresh and moist breath.<br/><br/>✔ Material: ABS + PP + PC + Silicon<br/>✔ Product size: 170 * 152 * 157mm<br/>✔ Water tank capacity: 380ml<br/>✔ Water use time: about 3-8 hours<br/>✔ Wind speed: level 3<br/>✔ Unit weight: 850g<br/>✔ Input voltage: DC 5V<br/>✔ Color: White<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Versatile functions and LED lights: This portable air cooler has three functions including air cooling, humidification and purification. Unlike other air conditioners, this USB fan can maintain indoor humidity without making your skin feel dry. It can also display warm LED lights at night.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint> ✔ Portable and easy to use: The portable USB air cooler is compact, portable and easily moved. You can put it in the kitchen, dormitory and office or wherever you like. In addition, you can take it with you when you are outdoors in the hot summer.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint> ✔ Fast cooling: This personal air cooler can quickly cool the hot air around you. With 3 fan speeds, you can choose the ideal wind force according to your needs. With this personal desktop fan, you can add ice or ice water to the water tank for faster cooling.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint> ✔ Energy saving and environmental protection: The evaporative air cooler and humidifier are Freon-free air conditioners, which can reduce energy consumption. It is supported by the USB port and can run for a long time after being filled with water. You can use this mini air cooler safely all night long because it is very environmentally friendly.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint> ✔ Ultra-quiet operation: This portable fan can work powerfully at low noise levels. In full operating mode, the quality of air cooling remains unaffected. This ultra-quiet air cooler allows you to sleep comfortably all night, with the right temperature and low noise.</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>desk fan usb quiet mini cooling battery handheld portable rechargeable turbo lcd touch screen, 3-speed mode easy to operate retro design 4inch bedroom office living room speeds turbofan 35w energy saving powered with led</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>11</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521585820217</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6954520668315</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, 4-In-1 Humidifier Cooler, 3-Speed Desktop Cooling Fan, Suitable For Home, Room, Office</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to stay cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air to your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy a fresh and moist breath.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, keep away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air and enjoy a healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy efficient and low carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>Mini personal air cooler designed for personal use, please place no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 4-in-1 design: This evaporative air cooler has portable fan cooling, spray humidification, air purification and 4-in-1 functions of 7 LED lights, which not only reduces the temperature, but also helps us avoid dry air. In addition, it has a 7-color LED ambient light, and a soft and colorful LED light built in to create a romantic atmosphere and provide you with a better sleeping environment.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 3 speed adjustment: Our mini air conditioner is designed with 3 speed modes, which can be freely adjusted according to your requirements (low / medium / high). If necessary, you can also adjust the wind direction to rotate vertically. (Note: Portable air coolers are not suitable for cooling the entire room.)</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Energy saving and health: This portable air cooler has low energy consumption and is freon-free. Not only does it protect the health of your family, it also consumes only 3.5 watts of power to minimize energy loss and protect the environment. Ideal for summer living room, bedroom, office, etc. cooling. Can also be used at work and travel.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Easy to operate and lightweight: Just add water or ice water, then plug the USB cable into a mobile power supply or any USB interface, and you can use the portable mini air cooler by pressing the function button.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: Our store uses international logistics, you can contact us at any time by email, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer is always the first, you can find yourself by searching for "DUYER" Favorite products, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>desk fan usb quiet mini cooling battery handheld portable rechargeable turbo lcd touch screen, 3-speed mode easy to operate retro design 4inch bedroom office living room speeds turbofan 35w energy saving powered with led</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>12</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521585821092</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6954520668339</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, Desktop Mini Air Conditioner Fan, Usb Cooling And Water Cooler Desktop Humidifier Fan, Office, Bedroom, Living Room, Kitchen And Outdoor</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to stay cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air to your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy a fresh and moist breath.<br/><br/>✔ Cooling fan and humidifier<br/>The air conditioner, portable evaporative air cooler and atomizing humidifier are combined into one, which can humidify the skin and air, keep away from the dry air, and enjoy the coolness of summer.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air and enjoy a healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy efficient and low carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Name: Desktop Cooler<br/>✔ Color: White<br/>✔ Material: ABS<br/>✔ Negative ion concentration: 3 million / cm3<br/>✔ Input voltage: 5V<br/>✔ Ozone concentration: <0.05PPM<br/>✔ Input current: 1.5-2A<br/>✔ Rated power: 5W<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Double protection of deep humidification: In addition to normal evaporative humidification, active atomization can be turned on</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>Yes, it can strengthen the humidifying effect to cope with the severe and hot summer.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Easy to operate and lightweight: Just add water or ice water, then plug the USB cable into a mobile power supply or any USB interface, and you can use the portable mini air cooler by pressing the function button.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Portable design: This personal air conditioner uses a mini-portable design, with a retractable handle on the top of the air cooler, which is only 7.2 inches high. It is very easy to carry to the office, bedroom, living room, kitchen and outdoor.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Energy saving and health: This portable air cooler has low energy consumption and is freon-free. It not only protects the health of your family, but also minimizes energy loss and protects the environment. Can also be used at work and travel.</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>desk fan usb quiet mini cooling battery handheld portable rechargeable turbo lcd touch screen, 3-speed mode easy to operate retro design 4inch bedroom office living room speeds turbofan 35w energy saving powered with led</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>13</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521585822622</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6954520668353</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Portable Air Cooler, Mini Air Conditioner, Touch Control 3 Speed Fan Speed, Usb Powered, For Home Office Outdoor</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to stay cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air to your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add water and ice to the water tank, then relax and enjoy a fresh and moist breath.<br/><br/>✔ Product name: USB Mini Cooler<br/>✔ Material: ABS material<br/>✔ Product size: 140 * 155 * 175mm<br/>✔ Power: 5W<br/>✔ Working voltage: 1A<br/>✔ Input voltage: 5V<br/>✔ Size: 170 * 170 * 205mm<br/><br/>✔ Packing list<br/>1 * Cooler<br/>1 * USB cable<br/>1 * Manual (Chinese and English)]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ With three functions of cooling, humidification and air purification, the wind speed can be adjusted in three speeds;</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Quiet use, free of freon in environmental protection and refrigeration;</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Built-in 160ml water tank, once filled, can last 8 hours;</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ USB charging or AC power supply; USB cable length: 85cm</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Use place: office, home living room, kitchen, bedroom, bathroom and home construction area, etc.</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>desk fan usb quiet mini cooling battery handheld portable rechargeable turbo lcd touch screen, 3-speed mode easy to operate retro design 4inch bedroom office living room speeds turbofan 35w energy saving powered with led</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>14</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>DUYER-521585823584</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>6954520668377</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Personal Air Cooler, Portable Mini Air Conditioner, 3-Speed Wind Speed, Liftable Handle Design, Usb Power Supply For Multiple Scenes, Office Desk, Dormitory Bedroom</Title>
        <Brand>DUYER</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[✔ You want to stay cool in the hot summer, but worry that it will cost a lot to run the air conditioner all day, and ordinary fans will only blow warm air to your face.<br/><br/>✔ Do you want a better way to calm down?<br/>Use our mini air cooler to get this personal space cooler to create your comfort zone. Just add it to the water tank, then relax and enjoy a fresh and moist breath.<br/><br/>✔ Fresh air and enjoy a healthy life<br/>It reduces the temperature by water evaporation and produces fresh air. Low power consumption and long humidification time! It is energy efficient and low carbon.<br/><br/>✔ Portable personal air cooler<br/>Mini personal air cooler designed for personal use, please place no more than 3 feet to 4 feet.<br/><br/>✔ Product name: Personal Ice Fan<br/>✔ Net weight: 650G<br/>✔ Blowing range: 40-60CM<br/>✔ Volume: 460ML<br/>✔ Working current: 500MA<br/>✔ Interface: 5V2A MICRO USB interface<br/>✔ Cooling power: 150-300W<br/>✔ Size: 13.1 * 13.1 * 17CM<br/>✔ Cooling range: 3-10 ° C (the actual temperature depends on the humidity and temperature of the use environment)<br/><br/>✔ Package includes:<br/>1 x air conditioner<br/>1 x USB data cable<br/>1 x instruction manual<br/><br/>✔ Note:<br/>There may be slight errors in the data due to manual measurements and different measurement tools.<br/>Due to different monitors, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 3-speed wind speed: personal ice fan, light wind speed: suitable for meditation sitting to drive out summer impetuousness; stroke speed: suitable for desks and tables; strong wind speed: suitable for sweltering dormitories, dissipating--heat.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Versatile: Small size, small footprint, easy to carry and move, and USB type, so it can be used not only in the office, bedroom, or home.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Energy saving and health: Small air circulator does not contain ozone refrigerant. It can protect the health of your family. This mini air conditioner is both space saving and economical. In the summer, it is the ideal gift for you, your family and friends.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ Multiple power supply methods: three power supply methods, you can use the USB port of mobile devices such as laptop computers to supply power. Use the charger to power from a wall outlet. When using mobile power, you don't have to worry about power failure.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>✔ 100% after-sales service: Our store uses international logistics, you can contact us at any time by email, we will answer your questions within 24 hours, the customer is always the first, you can find yourself by searching for "DUYER" Favorite products, I wish you a happy shopping!</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ZYC</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>desk fan usb quiet mini cooling battery handheld portable rechargeable turbo lcd touch screen, 3-speed mode easy to operate retro design 4inch bedroom office living room speeds turbofan 35w energy saving powered with led</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Mobile Air Conditioners</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>306929031</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Color</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
</AmazonEnvelope>
