<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf8"?>
<AmazonEnvelope>
  <Header>
    <DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion>
    <MerchantIdentifier>AEVNUXOBWGAO5</MerchantIdentifier>
  </Header>
  <MessageType>Product</MessageType>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>1</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>LDLL-551586328979-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>9859476757274</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Exercise Resistance Bands Set, Up To 100 Lbs Fitness Stretch Workout Bands Kit 11Pc With Fitness Tubes, For Home Gym Training Yoga Pilates</Title>
        <Brand>LDLL</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[★ Welcome to the home of LDXLR, we will show the best products and best service. Hope you have the best shopping experience and look forward to your visit.<br/><br/>-Are you sad because you can't exercise at home? Do you need a product to exercise without a gym?<br/><br/>-This fitness resistance band set allows you to feel like a gym anytime, anywhere. If you use it, you can exercise without restrictions. Different types of stretch bands can adapt to different muscle group exercises. Let your muscles gradually achieve the desired effect!<br/>-High-quality products can even guarantee quality, safety and non-toxic, it must be suitable for you, so you can easily use it. As long as there is a person at home, you can train whole body. Its different weight exercise belt configurations can be used by everyone, such as your partner or your child.<br/><br/>★ Specifications<br/>-Name: resistance band<br/>-Material: TPE<br/>-Resistance: 10 ~ 30 pounds<br/>-Uses: beautiful legs, slimming, core training, strength training<br/><br/>★ Reminder:<br/>-Due to manual measurement and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>-Due to different monitors, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product<br/>-After-sales service: The design of the resistance band takes durability and quality into consideration, so you can rest assured. If the product does not meet or exceed your expectations, please contact us first, we will solve the problem within 24 hours.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>★ 【Resistance Band Full Body Exercise】 High quality standard fitness belt set 5 resistance bands made of natural latex tubes, you can use different pounds of resistance bands to train for your physical fitness. You can also use different pounds depending on the position in which you need to exercise.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ 【Enjoy Fitness Anytime, Anywhere】 The simple design of the resistance band allows you to enjoy fitness anywhere in the house without being affected by the environment. You only need one person to exercise. The resistance band is easy to install, easy to use. You can use a door frame and a door latch as a fitness aid at home. If you lock it with foot and door locks, you can stretch your arms and body.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ 【Applicable For Every Fitness Level】 Whether you are a beginner or an expert, these resistance bands are made for you. All muscles can be trained. The included straps and handles make these straps extremely different from the standard straps. With other accessories, multi-functional fitness purposes can be achieved.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ 【Made From High Quality】Environmentally friendly that is extremely durable and the tapes will last a long time. Carefully constructed, safe for maximum pleasure and safety during training.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★【Satisfaction Guarantee】- Welcome to LDXLR's home. If the product does not meet or exceed your expectations, please contact us immediately. We will resolve this issue within 24 hours and hope our customers have the best shopping experience.</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>LDLL</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>resistance bands fitness exercise loop workout pull up assist stretching strength training/conditioning physical therapy butt glute legs whole building gym training yoga pilates physiotherapy recovery non-slip skin-friendly coresteady set</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Exercise Bands</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>3407931</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Size</VariationTheme>
                <Size>11-piece set</Size>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>2</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>LDLL-551586330167-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>9859476757663</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Portable Exercise Resistance Band Set,  Fitness Bands With 5 Fitness Tubes, Stretch Fitness Home Set Elastic Rope</Title>
        <Brand>LDLL</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[★ Welcome to the home of LDXLR, we will show the best products and best service. Hope you have the best shopping experience and look forward to your visit.<br/><br/>-Are you sad because you can't exercise at home? Do you need a product to exercise without a gym?<br/>-This fitness resistance band set allows you to feel like a gym anytime, anywhere. If you use it, you can exercise without restrictions. Different types of stretch bands can adapt to different muscle group exercises. Let your muscles gradually achieve the desired effect!<br/><br/>★ Specifications<br/>[Product name]; pull rope suit<br/>[Product Material]; TPE<br/>[Product size]; The length of the pull rope is 1.2 meters, the total length is 1.5 meters<br/>[Rally parameters]; yellow 8 lbs. Green 15 lbs. Red 20 lbs. Blue 25 lbs. Black 30 lbs<br/>[Suitable for the crowd]; men, women and children<br/><br/>★ Reminder:<br/>-Due to manual measurement and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>-Due to different monitors, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product<br/>-After-sales service: The design of the resistance band takes durability and quality into consideration, so you can rest assured. If the product does not meet or exceed your expectations, please contact us first, we will solve the problem within 24 hours.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>★ DISFRUTE DE LA APTITUD EN CUALQUIER MOMENTO, EN CUALQUIER LUGAR - ¿No tiene mucho tiempo? Ya sea en casa, en la oficina o de vacaciones, con las bandas de tubo en forma, ahora es posible entrenar en cualquier momento y en cualquier lugar.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ SISTEMA DE ENTRENAMIENTO DE CUERPO COMPLETO: cada conjunto incluye correas para el tobillo, agarres para las manos y un ancla de la puerta que hace que sea más fácil apuntar a diferentes grupos musculares, incluidos los bíceps y tríceps, espalda y hombros, pecho y piernas, o abdominales duros.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ CUALQUIERA DE SU FAMILIA PUEDE OBTENERLO: el uso a largo plazo puede ayudar a aliviar el estrés, mejorar la salud del cuerpo, estimular la circulación sanguínea, perder peso e incluso ayudar con muchos problemas de rehabilitación. Nuestras bandas de entrenamiento son de diferentes tamaños y adecuadas para mujeres, hombres, niños y ancianos. Puede entrenar con su familia en cualquier lugar, en cualquier momento.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ SEGURIDAD SIEMPRE ENTRENA CON: las bandas de entrenamiento están hechas de TPE para que pueda concentrarse en sus sesiones de entrenamiento con facilidad y, por lo tanto, sean particularmente resistentes a las rasgaduras. Además, las piezas de conexión se cosen extra fuerte, lo que evita que se rompan los ojales.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ GARANTÍA DE SATISFACCIÓN: Bienvenido a la casa de LDXLR. Si el producto no cumple o supera sus expectativas, contáctenos de inmediato. Resolveremos este problema dentro de las 24 horas y esperamos que nuestros clientes tengan la mejor experiencia de compra.</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>LDLL</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>resistance bands fitness exercise loop workout pull up assist stretching strength training/conditioning physical therapy butt glute legs whole building gym training yoga pilates physiotherapy recovery non-slip skin-friendly coresteady set</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Exercise Bands</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>3407931</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Size</VariationTheme>
                <Size>set</Size>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>3</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>LDLL-551586330969-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>9859476758394</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Resistance Bands Set, Household Pull Rope Set Non-slip Firm Durable Fitness Exercise  Bands, for Build Muscle Body Shaping</Title>
        <Brand>LDLL</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[★ Welcome to the home of LDXLR, we will show the best products and best service. Hope you have the best shopping experience and look forward to your visit.<br/><br/>-Are you sad because you can't exercise at home? Do you need a product to exercise without a gym?<br/>-This fitness resistance band set allows you to feel like a gym anytime, anywhere. If you use it, you can exercise without restrictions. Different types of stretch bands can adapt to different muscle group exercises. Let your muscles gradually achieve the desired effect!<br/><br/>★ Specifications<br/>-Product name: Pull rope set<br/>-Product material: latex<br/>-Tensile parameters: yellow 10 pounds, blue 20 pounds, green 30 pounds, black 40 pounds, red 50 pounds<br/>-Suitable for the crowd: men, women and children<br/>-Product function: fitness, body shaping, strength training<br/><br/>★ Reminder:<br/>-Due to manual measurement and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>-Due to different monitors, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product<br/>-After-sales service: The design of the resistance band takes durability and quality into consideration, so you can rest assured. If the product does not meet or exceed your expectations, please contact us first, we will solve the problem within 24 hours.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>★ FULL BODY WORKOUT SYSTEM - Each set includes ankle straps, hand grips, and a door anchor that make it easier to target different muscle groups, including biceps and triceps, back and shoulders, chest and legs, or rock-hard abdominals.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ APPLICABLE FOR EVERY FITNESS LEVEL -  Whether you are a beginner or an expert, these resistance bands are made for you. All muscles can be trained. The included straps and handles make these straps extremely different from the standard straps. With other accessories, multi-functional fitness purposes can be achieved.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ GYM IN YOUR POCKE - Put these resistance bands in pocket or the lovely black carrying pouch then you would own a potable gym. These lightweight bands could let you do exercise wherever you want.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ IDEA FOR ALL WORKOUTS - Our versatile workout bands for women, men and children can be used in your cross-fit, Pilates, yoga,beach body and even dance and ballet routines to get integrated.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ SATISFACTION GUARANTEE - Welcome to LDXLR's home. If the product does not meet or exceed your expectations, please contact us immediately. We will resolve this issue within 24 hours and hope our customers have the best shopping experience.</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>LDLL</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>resistance bands fitness exercise loop workout pull up assist stretching strength training/conditioning physical therapy butt glute legs whole building gym training yoga pilates physiotherapy recovery non-slip skin-friendly coresteady set</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Exercise Bands</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>3407931</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Size</VariationTheme>
                <Size>150LB</Size>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>4</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>LDLL-551586331432-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>9859476758431</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Exercise Resistance Bands Set, Elastic Pull Rope 11pcs Fitness Stretch Workout Bands,  for Resistance Training,physical Therapy,men and Women</Title>
        <Brand>LDLL</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[★ Welcome to the home of LDXLR, we will show the best products and best service. Hope you have the best shopping experience and look forward to your visit.<br/><br/>-Are you sad because you can't exercise at home? Do you need a product to exercise without a gym?<br/>-This fitness resistance band set allows you to feel like a gym anytime, anywhere. If you use it, you can exercise without restrictions. Different types of stretch bands can adapt to different muscle group exercises. Let your muscles gradually achieve the desired effect!<br/><br/>★ Specifications<br/>-Product name: Pull rope set<br/>-Suitable for the crowd: men, women and children<br/>-Product function: fitness, body shaping, strength training<br/><br/>★ Reminder:<br/>-Due to manual measurement and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>-Due to different monitors, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product<br/>-After-sales service: The design of the resistance band takes durability and quality into consideration, so you can rest assured. If the product does not meet or exceed your expectations, please contact us first, we will solve the problem within 24 hours.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>★ APPLICABLE FOR EVERY FITNESS LEVEL - Whether you are a beginner or an expert, these resistance bands are made for you. All muscles can be trained. The included straps and handles make these straps extremely different from the standard straps. With other accessories, multi-functional fitness purposes can be achieved.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ FASHION SPORTS FAN - Body shaping and beautifying hip curve. What you need is just a stretch hip. Built-in non-slip rubber strip,  classic colors and matching colors, it becomes fashionable and trendy in seconds.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ ENJOY FITNESS ANYTIME, ANYWHERE - The simple design of the resistance band allows you to enjoy fitness anywhere in the house without being affected by the environment. You only need one person to exercise. The resistance band is easy to install, easy to use. You can use a door frame and a door latch as a fitness aid at home.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ SUITABLE FOR EVERYONE - can help everyone – male or female, professional athlete or beginner. You can use the set for yoga, warming up before exercising, strength training or physical therapy rehabilitation.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ SATISFACTION GUARANTEE - Welcome to LDXLR's home. If the product does not meet or exceed your expectations, please contact us immediately. We will resolve this issue within 24 hours and hope our customers have the best shopping experience.</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>LDLL</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>resistance bands fitness exercise loop workout pull up assist stretching strength training/conditioning physical therapy butt glute legs whole building gym training yoga pilates physiotherapy recovery non-slip skin-friendly coresteady set</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Exercise Bands</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>3407931</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Size</VariationTheme>
                <Size>set</Size>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>5</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>LDLL-551586331955-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>9859476758455</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Resistance Exercise Band Set of 5, High Strength Fitness Pull Rope Natural Latex Workout Bands Fat Burning Arm Fitness Equipment</Title>
        <Brand>LDLL</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[★ Welcome to the home of LDXLR, we will show the best products and best service. Hope you have the best shopping experience and look forward to your visit.<br/><br/>-Are you sad because you can't exercise at home? Do you need a product to exercise without a gym?<br/>-This fitness resistance band set allows you to feel like a gym anytime, anywhere. If you use it, you can exercise without restrictions. Different types of stretch bands can adapt to different muscle group exercises. Let your muscles gradually achieve the desired effect!<br/><br/>★ Specifications<br/>-Product name: resistance band<br/>-Material: Latex<br/>-Suitable for the crowd: men, women and children<br/>-Product function: fitness, body shaping, strength training<br/>-colour:<br/>(Yellow) 5 * 8 * 1200mm<br/>(Green) 6 * 9 * 1200mm<br/>(Red) 5 * 9 * 1200mm<br/>(Blue) 5 * 10 * 1200mm<br/>(Black) 5 * 11 * 1200mm<br/><br/>★ Reminder:<br/>-Due to manual measurement and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>-Due to different monitors, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product<br/>-After-sales service: The design of the resistance band takes durability and quality into consideration, so you can rest assured. If the product does not meet or exceed your expectations, please contact us first, we will solve the problem within 24 hours.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>★ APPLICABLE FOR EVERY FITNESS LEVEL -  Whether you are a beginner or an expert, these resistance bands are made for you. All muscles can be trained. The included straps and handles make these straps extremely different from the standard straps. With other accessories, multi-functional fitness purposes can be achieved.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ FASHION SPORTS FAN - Body shaping and beautifying hip curve. What you need is just a stretch hip. Built-in non-slip rubber strip,  classic colors and matching colors, it becomes fashionable and trendy in seconds.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ GYM IN YOUR POCKE - Put these resistance bands in pocket or the lovely black carrying pouch then you would own a potable gym. These lightweight bands could let you do exercise wherever you want.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ IDEA FOR ALL WORKOUTS - Our versatile workout bands for women, men and children can be used in your cross-fit, Pilates, yoga,beach body and even dance and ballet routines to get integrated.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ SATISFACTION GUARANTEE - Welcome to LDXLR's home. If the product does not meet or exceed your expectations, please contact us immediately. We will resolve this issue within 24 hours and hope our customers have the best shopping experience.</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>LDLL</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>resistance bands fitness exercise loop workout pull up assist stretching strength training/conditioning physical therapy butt glute legs whole building gym training yoga pilates physiotherapy recovery non-slip skin-friendly coresteady set</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Exercise Bands</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>3407931</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Size</VariationTheme>
                <Size>Set of 5</Size>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>6</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>LDLL-551586332263-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>9859476758479</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Exercise Resistance Bands Set, Multifunction Free Adjustmen Fitness Stretch Workout Bands with Safety Lock for Men Women</Title>
        <Brand>LDLL</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[★ Welcome to the home of LDXLR, we will show the best products and best service. Hope you have the best shopping experience and look forward to your visit.<br/><br/>-Are you sad because you can't exercise at home? Do you need a product to exercise without a gym?<br/>-This fitness resistance band set allows you to feel like a gym anytime, anywhere. If you use it, you can exercise without restrictions. Different types of stretch bands can adapt to different muscle group exercises. Let your muscles gradually achieve the desired effect!<br/><br/>★ Specifications<br/>-Product name: resistance band<br/>-Total length: 1.5m<br/>-Rope length: 1.25m<br/>-Material: ABS new material + NBR foam + hose<br/>-Suitable for the crowd: men, women and children<br/>-Product function: fitness, body shaping, strength training<br/><br/>★ Reminder:<br/>-Due to manual measurement and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>-Due to different monitors, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product<br/>-After-sales service: The design of the resistance band takes durability and quality into consideration, so you can rest assured. If the product does not meet or exceed your expectations, please contact us first, we will solve the problem within 24 hours.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>★ FASHION SPORTS FAN - Body shaping and beautifying hip curve. What you need is just a stretch hip. Built-in non-slip rubber strip,  classic colors and matching colors, it becomes fashionable and trendy in seconds.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ Convenient and Flexible - Easy to carry, you can use it anytime, anywhere. Train at home, at the gym or while traveling. Can be used for crossfit, yoga, Pilates, fitness. Lose weight or strengthen muscles.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ Versatile -  Ideal for strength training, physical therapy, rehabilitation, Pilates and stretching. Add them to any strength routine to challenge your muscles, or to aid stretching to increase flexibility and range of motion.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ SAFETY LOCK - Easy to assemble and disassemble, one-piece anti-break design, 360 ° rotation to prevent the hose from buckling</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ SATISFACTION GUARANTEE - Welcome to LDXLR's home. If the product does not meet or exceed your expectations, please contact us immediately. We will resolve this issue within 24 hours and hope our customers have the best shopping experience.</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>LDLL</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>resistance bands fitness exercise loop workout pull up assist stretching strength training/conditioning physical therapy butt glute legs whole building gym training yoga pilates physiotherapy recovery non-slip skin-friendly coresteady set</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Exercise Bands</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>3407931</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Size</VariationTheme>
                <Size>Set of 3</Size>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>7</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>LDLL-551586332625-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>9859476758493</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Exercise Resistance Bands Set, Multifunction Fitness Stretch Workout Bands 11pc, with Fitness Tubes, Foam Handles, Ankle Straps,bag</Title>
        <Brand>LDLL</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[★ Welcome to the home of LDXLR, we will show the best products and best service. Hope you have the best shopping experience and look forward to your visit.<br/><br/>-Are you sad because you can't exercise at home? Do you need a product to exercise without a gym?<br/>-This fitness resistance band set allows you to feel like a gym anytime, anywhere. If you use it, you can exercise without restrictions.<br/>-High-quality products can even guarantee quality, safety and non-toxic, it must be suitable for you, so you can easily use it. As long as there is a person at home, you can train whole body<br/><br/>★ Specifications<br/>-Product name: resistance band<br/>-Material: Latex<br/>-Suitable for the crowd: men, women and children<br/>-Product function: fitness, body shaping, strength training<br/><br/>★ Reminder:<br/>-Due to manual measurement and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>-Due to different monitors, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product<br/>-After-sales service: The design of the resistance band takes durability and quality into consideration, so you can rest assured. If the product does not meet or exceed your expectations, please contact us first, we will solve the problem within 24 hours.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>★ APPLICABLE FOR EVERY FITNESS LEVEL -  Whether you are a beginner or an expert, these resistance bands are made for you. All muscles can be trained. The included straps and handles make these straps extremely different from the standard straps. With other accessories, multi-functional fitness purposes can be achieved.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ FASHION SPORTS FAN - Body shaping and beautifying hip curve. What you need is just a stretch hip. Built-in non-slip rubber strip,  classic colors and matching colors, it becomes fashionable and trendy in seconds.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ FULL BODY WORKOUT SYSTEM - Each set includes ankle straps, hand grips, and a door anchor that make it easier to target different muscle groups, including biceps and triceps, back and shoulders, chest and legs, or rock-hard abdominals.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ GYM IN YOUR POCKE - Put these resistance bands in pocket or the lovely black carrying pouch then you would own a potable gym. These lightweight bands could let you do exercise wherever you want.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ SATISFACTION GUARANTEE - Welcome to LDXLR's home. If the product does not meet or exceed your expectations, please contact us immediately. We will resolve this issue within 24 hours and hope our customers have the best shopping experience.</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>LDLL</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>resistance bands fitness exercise loop workout pull up assist stretching strength training/conditioning physical therapy butt glute legs whole building gym training yoga pilates physiotherapy recovery non-slip skin-friendly coresteady set</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Exercise Bands</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>3407931</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Size</VariationTheme>
                <Size>set</Size>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>8</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>LDLL-551586332856-0</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>9859476758516</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Portable Exercise Resistance Band Set, Colorful Elastic Pull Rope Exercise Stretch Fitness Home Set For Yoga Pilates Crossfit 
</Title>
        <Brand>LDLL</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[★ Welcome to the home of LDXLR, we will show the best products and best service. Hope you have the best shopping experience and look forward to your visit.<br/><br/>-Are you sad because you can't exercise at home? Do you need a product to exercise without a gym?<br/>-This fitness resistance band set allows you to feel like a gym anytime, anywhere. If you use it, you can exercise without restrictions.<br/>-High-quality products can even guarantee quality, safety and non-toxic, it must be suitable for you, so you can easily use it. As long as there is a person at home, you can train whole body<br/><br/>★ Specifications<br/>-Product name: resistance band<br/>-Material: TPE<br/>-Suitable for the crowd: men, women and children<br/>-Packing: OPP bag packaging<br/>-Product function: fitness, body shaping, strength training<br/><br/>★ Reminder:<br/>-Due to manual measurement and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>-Due to different monitors, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product<br/>-After-sales service: The design of the resistance band takes durability and quality into consideration, so you can rest assured. If the product does not meet or exceed your expectations, please contact us first, we will solve the problem within 24 hours.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>★ APPLICABLE FOR EVERY FITNESS LEVEL - Whether you are a beginner or an expert, these resistance bands are made for you. All muscles can be trained. The included straps and handles make these straps extremely different from the standard straps. With other accessories, multi-functional fitness purposes can be achieved.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ FASHION SPORTS FAN - Body shaping and beautifying hip curve. What you need is just a stretch hip. Built-in non-slip rubber strip,  classic colors and matching colors, it becomes fashionable and trendy in seconds.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ Convenient and Flexible - Easy to carry, you can use it anytime, anywhere. Train at home, at the gym or while traveling. Can be used for crossfit, yoga, Pilates, fitness. Lose weight or strengthen muscles.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ ENJOY FITNESS ANYTIME, ANYWHERE - The simple design of the resistance band allows you to enjoy fitness anywhere in the house without being affected by the environment. You only need one person to exercise. The resistance band is easy to install, easy to use. You can use a door frame and a door latch as a fitness aid at home.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ SUITABLE FOR EVERYONE - can help everyone – male or female, professional athlete or beginner. You can use the set for yoga, warming up before exercising, strength training or physical therapy rehabilitation.</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>LDLL</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>resistance bands fitness exercise loop workout pull up assist stretching strength training/conditioning physical therapy butt glute legs whole building gym training yoga pilates physiotherapy recovery non-slip skin-friendly coresteady set</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Exercise Bands</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>3407931</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Size</VariationTheme>
                <Size>Set of 7</Size>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>child</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>9</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>LDLL-551586328979</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>9859476757267</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Exercise Resistance Bands Set, Up To 100 Lbs Fitness Stretch Workout Bands Kit 11Pc With Fitness Tubes, For Home Gym Training Yoga Pilates</Title>
        <Brand>LDLL</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[★ Welcome to the home of LDXLR, we will show the best products and best service. Hope you have the best shopping experience and look forward to your visit.<br/><br/>-Are you sad because you can't exercise at home? Do you need a product to exercise without a gym?<br/><br/>-This fitness resistance band set allows you to feel like a gym anytime, anywhere. If you use it, you can exercise without restrictions. Different types of stretch bands can adapt to different muscle group exercises. Let your muscles gradually achieve the desired effect!<br/>-High-quality products can even guarantee quality, safety and non-toxic, it must be suitable for you, so you can easily use it. As long as there is a person at home, you can train whole body. Its different weight exercise belt configurations can be used by everyone, such as your partner or your child.<br/><br/>★ Specifications<br/>-Name: resistance band<br/>-Material: TPE<br/>-Resistance: 10 ~ 30 pounds<br/>-Uses: beautiful legs, slimming, core training, strength training<br/><br/>★ Reminder:<br/>-Due to manual measurement and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>-Due to different monitors, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product<br/>-After-sales service: The design of the resistance band takes durability and quality into consideration, so you can rest assured. If the product does not meet or exceed your expectations, please contact us first, we will solve the problem within 24 hours.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>★ 【Resistance Band Full Body Exercise】 High quality standard fitness belt set 5 resistance bands made of natural latex tubes, you can use different pounds of resistance bands to train for your physical fitness. You can also use different pounds depending on the position in which you need to exercise.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ 【Enjoy Fitness Anytime, Anywhere】 The simple design of the resistance band allows you to enjoy fitness anywhere in the house without being affected by the environment. You only need one person to exercise. The resistance band is easy to install, easy to use. You can use a door frame and a door latch as a fitness aid at home. If you lock it with foot and door locks, you can stretch your arms and body.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ 【Applicable For Every Fitness Level】 Whether you are a beginner or an expert, these resistance bands are made for you. All muscles can be trained. The included straps and handles make these straps extremely different from the standard straps. With other accessories, multi-functional fitness purposes can be achieved.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ 【Made From High Quality】Environmentally friendly that is extremely durable and the tapes will last a long time. Carefully constructed, safe for maximum pleasure and safety during training.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★【Satisfaction Guarantee】- Welcome to LDXLR's home. If the product does not meet or exceed your expectations, please contact us immediately. We will resolve this issue within 24 hours and hope our customers have the best shopping experience.</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>LDLL</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>resistance bands fitness exercise loop workout pull up assist stretching strength training/conditioning physical therapy butt glute legs whole building gym training yoga pilates physiotherapy recovery non-slip skin-friendly coresteady set</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Exercise Bands</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>3407931</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Size</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>10</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>LDLL-551586330167</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>9859476757656</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Portable Exercise Resistance Band Set,  Fitness Bands With 5 Fitness Tubes, Stretch Fitness Home Set Elastic Rope</Title>
        <Brand>LDLL</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[★ Welcome to the home of LDXLR, we will show the best products and best service. Hope you have the best shopping experience and look forward to your visit.<br/><br/>-Are you sad because you can't exercise at home? Do you need a product to exercise without a gym?<br/>-This fitness resistance band set allows you to feel like a gym anytime, anywhere. If you use it, you can exercise without restrictions. Different types of stretch bands can adapt to different muscle group exercises. Let your muscles gradually achieve the desired effect!<br/><br/>★ Specifications<br/>[Product name]; pull rope suit<br/>[Product Material]; TPE<br/>[Product size]; The length of the pull rope is 1.2 meters, the total length is 1.5 meters<br/>[Rally parameters]; yellow 8 lbs. Green 15 lbs. Red 20 lbs. Blue 25 lbs. Black 30 lbs<br/>[Suitable for the crowd]; men, women and children<br/><br/>★ Reminder:<br/>-Due to manual measurement and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>-Due to different monitors, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product<br/>-After-sales service: The design of the resistance band takes durability and quality into consideration, so you can rest assured. If the product does not meet or exceed your expectations, please contact us first, we will solve the problem within 24 hours.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>★ DISFRUTE DE LA APTITUD EN CUALQUIER MOMENTO, EN CUALQUIER LUGAR - ¿No tiene mucho tiempo? Ya sea en casa, en la oficina o de vacaciones, con las bandas de tubo en forma, ahora es posible entrenar en cualquier momento y en cualquier lugar.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ SISTEMA DE ENTRENAMIENTO DE CUERPO COMPLETO: cada conjunto incluye correas para el tobillo, agarres para las manos y un ancla de la puerta que hace que sea más fácil apuntar a diferentes grupos musculares, incluidos los bíceps y tríceps, espalda y hombros, pecho y piernas, o abdominales duros.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ CUALQUIERA DE SU FAMILIA PUEDE OBTENERLO: el uso a largo plazo puede ayudar a aliviar el estrés, mejorar la salud del cuerpo, estimular la circulación sanguínea, perder peso e incluso ayudar con muchos problemas de rehabilitación. Nuestras bandas de entrenamiento son de diferentes tamaños y adecuadas para mujeres, hombres, niños y ancianos. Puede entrenar con su familia en cualquier lugar, en cualquier momento.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ SEGURIDAD SIEMPRE ENTRENA CON: las bandas de entrenamiento están hechas de TPE para que pueda concentrarse en sus sesiones de entrenamiento con facilidad y, por lo tanto, sean particularmente resistentes a las rasgaduras. Además, las piezas de conexión se cosen extra fuerte, lo que evita que se rompan los ojales.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ GARANTÍA DE SATISFACCIÓN: Bienvenido a la casa de LDXLR. Si el producto no cumple o supera sus expectativas, contáctenos de inmediato. Resolveremos este problema dentro de las 24 horas y esperamos que nuestros clientes tengan la mejor experiencia de compra.</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>LDLL</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>resistance bands fitness exercise loop workout pull up assist stretching strength training/conditioning physical therapy butt glute legs whole building gym training yoga pilates physiotherapy recovery non-slip skin-friendly coresteady set</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Exercise Bands</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>3407931</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Size</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>11</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>LDLL-551586330969</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>9859476758387</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Resistance Bands Set, Household Pull Rope Set Non-slip Firm Durable Fitness Exercise  Bands, for Build Muscle Body Shaping</Title>
        <Brand>LDLL</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[★ Welcome to the home of LDXLR, we will show the best products and best service. Hope you have the best shopping experience and look forward to your visit.<br/><br/>-Are you sad because you can't exercise at home? Do you need a product to exercise without a gym?<br/>-This fitness resistance band set allows you to feel like a gym anytime, anywhere. If you use it, you can exercise without restrictions. Different types of stretch bands can adapt to different muscle group exercises. Let your muscles gradually achieve the desired effect!<br/><br/>★ Specifications<br/>-Product name: Pull rope set<br/>-Product material: latex<br/>-Tensile parameters: yellow 10 pounds, blue 20 pounds, green 30 pounds, black 40 pounds, red 50 pounds<br/>-Suitable for the crowd: men, women and children<br/>-Product function: fitness, body shaping, strength training<br/><br/>★ Reminder:<br/>-Due to manual measurement and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>-Due to different monitors, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product<br/>-After-sales service: The design of the resistance band takes durability and quality into consideration, so you can rest assured. If the product does not meet or exceed your expectations, please contact us first, we will solve the problem within 24 hours.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>★ FULL BODY WORKOUT SYSTEM - Each set includes ankle straps, hand grips, and a door anchor that make it easier to target different muscle groups, including biceps and triceps, back and shoulders, chest and legs, or rock-hard abdominals.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ APPLICABLE FOR EVERY FITNESS LEVEL -  Whether you are a beginner or an expert, these resistance bands are made for you. All muscles can be trained. The included straps and handles make these straps extremely different from the standard straps. With other accessories, multi-functional fitness purposes can be achieved.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ GYM IN YOUR POCKE - Put these resistance bands in pocket or the lovely black carrying pouch then you would own a potable gym. These lightweight bands could let you do exercise wherever you want.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ IDEA FOR ALL WORKOUTS - Our versatile workout bands for women, men and children can be used in your cross-fit, Pilates, yoga,beach body and even dance and ballet routines to get integrated.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ SATISFACTION GUARANTEE - Welcome to LDXLR's home. If the product does not meet or exceed your expectations, please contact us immediately. We will resolve this issue within 24 hours and hope our customers have the best shopping experience.</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>LDLL</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>resistance bands fitness exercise loop workout pull up assist stretching strength training/conditioning physical therapy butt glute legs whole building gym training yoga pilates physiotherapy recovery non-slip skin-friendly coresteady set</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Exercise Bands</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>3407931</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Size</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>12</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>LDLL-551586331432</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>9859476758424</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Exercise Resistance Bands Set, Elastic Pull Rope 11pcs Fitness Stretch Workout Bands,  for Resistance Training,physical Therapy,men and Women</Title>
        <Brand>LDLL</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[★ Welcome to the home of LDXLR, we will show the best products and best service. Hope you have the best shopping experience and look forward to your visit.<br/><br/>-Are you sad because you can't exercise at home? Do you need a product to exercise without a gym?<br/>-This fitness resistance band set allows you to feel like a gym anytime, anywhere. If you use it, you can exercise without restrictions. Different types of stretch bands can adapt to different muscle group exercises. Let your muscles gradually achieve the desired effect!<br/><br/>★ Specifications<br/>-Product name: Pull rope set<br/>-Suitable for the crowd: men, women and children<br/>-Product function: fitness, body shaping, strength training<br/><br/>★ Reminder:<br/>-Due to manual measurement and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>-Due to different monitors, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product<br/>-After-sales service: The design of the resistance band takes durability and quality into consideration, so you can rest assured. If the product does not meet or exceed your expectations, please contact us first, we will solve the problem within 24 hours.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>★ APPLICABLE FOR EVERY FITNESS LEVEL - Whether you are a beginner or an expert, these resistance bands are made for you. All muscles can be trained. The included straps and handles make these straps extremely different from the standard straps. With other accessories, multi-functional fitness purposes can be achieved.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ FASHION SPORTS FAN - Body shaping and beautifying hip curve. What you need is just a stretch hip. Built-in non-slip rubber strip,  classic colors and matching colors, it becomes fashionable and trendy in seconds.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ ENJOY FITNESS ANYTIME, ANYWHERE - The simple design of the resistance band allows you to enjoy fitness anywhere in the house without being affected by the environment. You only need one person to exercise. The resistance band is easy to install, easy to use. You can use a door frame and a door latch as a fitness aid at home.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ SUITABLE FOR EVERYONE - can help everyone – male or female, professional athlete or beginner. You can use the set for yoga, warming up before exercising, strength training or physical therapy rehabilitation.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ SATISFACTION GUARANTEE - Welcome to LDXLR's home. If the product does not meet or exceed your expectations, please contact us immediately. We will resolve this issue within 24 hours and hope our customers have the best shopping experience.</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>LDLL</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>resistance bands fitness exercise loop workout pull up assist stretching strength training/conditioning physical therapy butt glute legs whole building gym training yoga pilates physiotherapy recovery non-slip skin-friendly coresteady set</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Exercise Bands</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>3407931</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Size</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>13</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>LDLL-551586331955</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>9859476758448</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Resistance Exercise Band Set of 5, High Strength Fitness Pull Rope Natural Latex Workout Bands Fat Burning Arm Fitness Equipment</Title>
        <Brand>LDLL</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[★ Welcome to the home of LDXLR, we will show the best products and best service. Hope you have the best shopping experience and look forward to your visit.<br/><br/>-Are you sad because you can't exercise at home? Do you need a product to exercise without a gym?<br/>-This fitness resistance band set allows you to feel like a gym anytime, anywhere. If you use it, you can exercise without restrictions. Different types of stretch bands can adapt to different muscle group exercises. Let your muscles gradually achieve the desired effect!<br/><br/>★ Specifications<br/>-Product name: resistance band<br/>-Material: Latex<br/>-Suitable for the crowd: men, women and children<br/>-Product function: fitness, body shaping, strength training<br/>-colour:<br/>(Yellow) 5 * 8 * 1200mm<br/>(Green) 6 * 9 * 1200mm<br/>(Red) 5 * 9 * 1200mm<br/>(Blue) 5 * 10 * 1200mm<br/>(Black) 5 * 11 * 1200mm<br/><br/>★ Reminder:<br/>-Due to manual measurement and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>-Due to different monitors, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product<br/>-After-sales service: The design of the resistance band takes durability and quality into consideration, so you can rest assured. If the product does not meet or exceed your expectations, please contact us first, we will solve the problem within 24 hours.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>★ APPLICABLE FOR EVERY FITNESS LEVEL -  Whether you are a beginner or an expert, these resistance bands are made for you. All muscles can be trained. The included straps and handles make these straps extremely different from the standard straps. With other accessories, multi-functional fitness purposes can be achieved.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ FASHION SPORTS FAN - Body shaping and beautifying hip curve. What you need is just a stretch hip. Built-in non-slip rubber strip,  classic colors and matching colors, it becomes fashionable and trendy in seconds.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ GYM IN YOUR POCKE - Put these resistance bands in pocket or the lovely black carrying pouch then you would own a potable gym. These lightweight bands could let you do exercise wherever you want.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ IDEA FOR ALL WORKOUTS - Our versatile workout bands for women, men and children can be used in your cross-fit, Pilates, yoga,beach body and even dance and ballet routines to get integrated.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ SATISFACTION GUARANTEE - Welcome to LDXLR's home. If the product does not meet or exceed your expectations, please contact us immediately. We will resolve this issue within 24 hours and hope our customers have the best shopping experience.</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>LDLL</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>resistance bands fitness exercise loop workout pull up assist stretching strength training/conditioning physical therapy butt glute legs whole building gym training yoga pilates physiotherapy recovery non-slip skin-friendly coresteady set</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Exercise Bands</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>3407931</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Size</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>14</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>LDLL-551586332263</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>9859476758462</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Exercise Resistance Bands Set, Multifunction Free Adjustmen Fitness Stretch Workout Bands with Safety Lock for Men Women</Title>
        <Brand>LDLL</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[★ Welcome to the home of LDXLR, we will show the best products and best service. Hope you have the best shopping experience and look forward to your visit.<br/><br/>-Are you sad because you can't exercise at home? Do you need a product to exercise without a gym?<br/>-This fitness resistance band set allows you to feel like a gym anytime, anywhere. If you use it, you can exercise without restrictions. Different types of stretch bands can adapt to different muscle group exercises. Let your muscles gradually achieve the desired effect!<br/><br/>★ Specifications<br/>-Product name: resistance band<br/>-Total length: 1.5m<br/>-Rope length: 1.25m<br/>-Material: ABS new material + NBR foam + hose<br/>-Suitable for the crowd: men, women and children<br/>-Product function: fitness, body shaping, strength training<br/><br/>★ Reminder:<br/>-Due to manual measurement and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>-Due to different monitors, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product<br/>-After-sales service: The design of the resistance band takes durability and quality into consideration, so you can rest assured. If the product does not meet or exceed your expectations, please contact us first, we will solve the problem within 24 hours.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>★ FASHION SPORTS FAN - Body shaping and beautifying hip curve. What you need is just a stretch hip. Built-in non-slip rubber strip,  classic colors and matching colors, it becomes fashionable and trendy in seconds.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ Convenient and Flexible - Easy to carry, you can use it anytime, anywhere. Train at home, at the gym or while traveling. Can be used for crossfit, yoga, Pilates, fitness. Lose weight or strengthen muscles.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ Versatile -  Ideal for strength training, physical therapy, rehabilitation, Pilates and stretching. Add them to any strength routine to challenge your muscles, or to aid stretching to increase flexibility and range of motion.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ SAFETY LOCK - Easy to assemble and disassemble, one-piece anti-break design, 360 ° rotation to prevent the hose from buckling</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ SATISFACTION GUARANTEE - Welcome to LDXLR's home. If the product does not meet or exceed your expectations, please contact us immediately. We will resolve this issue within 24 hours and hope our customers have the best shopping experience.</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>LDLL</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>resistance bands fitness exercise loop workout pull up assist stretching strength training/conditioning physical therapy butt glute legs whole building gym training yoga pilates physiotherapy recovery non-slip skin-friendly coresteady set</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Exercise Bands</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>3407931</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Size</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>15</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>LDLL-551586332625</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>9859476758486</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Exercise Resistance Bands Set, Multifunction Fitness Stretch Workout Bands 11pc, with Fitness Tubes, Foam Handles, Ankle Straps,bag</Title>
        <Brand>LDLL</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[★ Welcome to the home of LDXLR, we will show the best products and best service. Hope you have the best shopping experience and look forward to your visit.<br/><br/>-Are you sad because you can't exercise at home? Do you need a product to exercise without a gym?<br/>-This fitness resistance band set allows you to feel like a gym anytime, anywhere. If you use it, you can exercise without restrictions.<br/>-High-quality products can even guarantee quality, safety and non-toxic, it must be suitable for you, so you can easily use it. As long as there is a person at home, you can train whole body<br/><br/>★ Specifications<br/>-Product name: resistance band<br/>-Material: Latex<br/>-Suitable for the crowd: men, women and children<br/>-Product function: fitness, body shaping, strength training<br/><br/>★ Reminder:<br/>-Due to manual measurement and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>-Due to different monitors, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product<br/>-After-sales service: The design of the resistance band takes durability and quality into consideration, so you can rest assured. If the product does not meet or exceed your expectations, please contact us first, we will solve the problem within 24 hours.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>★ APPLICABLE FOR EVERY FITNESS LEVEL -  Whether you are a beginner or an expert, these resistance bands are made for you. All muscles can be trained. The included straps and handles make these straps extremely different from the standard straps. With other accessories, multi-functional fitness purposes can be achieved.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ FASHION SPORTS FAN - Body shaping and beautifying hip curve. What you need is just a stretch hip. Built-in non-slip rubber strip,  classic colors and matching colors, it becomes fashionable and trendy in seconds.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ FULL BODY WORKOUT SYSTEM - Each set includes ankle straps, hand grips, and a door anchor that make it easier to target different muscle groups, including biceps and triceps, back and shoulders, chest and legs, or rock-hard abdominals.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ GYM IN YOUR POCKE - Put these resistance bands in pocket or the lovely black carrying pouch then you would own a potable gym. These lightweight bands could let you do exercise wherever you want.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ SATISFACTION GUARANTEE - Welcome to LDXLR's home. If the product does not meet or exceed your expectations, please contact us immediately. We will resolve this issue within 24 hours and hope our customers have the best shopping experience.</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>LDLL</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>resistance bands fitness exercise loop workout pull up assist stretching strength training/conditioning physical therapy butt glute legs whole building gym training yoga pilates physiotherapy recovery non-slip skin-friendly coresteady set</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Exercise Bands</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>3407931</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Size</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>16</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>LDLL-551586332856</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>9859476758509</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Portable Exercise Resistance Band Set, Colorful Elastic Pull Rope Exercise Stretch Fitness Home Set For Yoga Pilates Crossfit 
</Title>
        <Brand>LDLL</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[★ Welcome to the home of LDXLR, we will show the best products and best service. Hope you have the best shopping experience and look forward to your visit.<br/><br/>-Are you sad because you can't exercise at home? Do you need a product to exercise without a gym?<br/>-This fitness resistance band set allows you to feel like a gym anytime, anywhere. If you use it, you can exercise without restrictions.<br/>-High-quality products can even guarantee quality, safety and non-toxic, it must be suitable for you, so you can easily use it. As long as there is a person at home, you can train whole body<br/><br/>★ Specifications<br/>-Product name: resistance band<br/>-Material: TPE<br/>-Suitable for the crowd: men, women and children<br/>-Packing: OPP bag packaging<br/>-Product function: fitness, body shaping, strength training<br/><br/>★ Reminder:<br/>-Due to manual measurement and different measurement tools, there may be subtle errors in the data.<br/>-Due to different monitors, there may be slight color differences. Please refer to the actual product<br/>-After-sales service: The design of the resistance band takes durability and quality into consideration, so you can rest assured. If the product does not meet or exceed your expectations, please contact us first, we will solve the problem within 24 hours.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>★ APPLICABLE FOR EVERY FITNESS LEVEL - Whether you are a beginner or an expert, these resistance bands are made for you. All muscles can be trained. The included straps and handles make these straps extremely different from the standard straps. With other accessories, multi-functional fitness purposes can be achieved.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ FASHION SPORTS FAN - Body shaping and beautifying hip curve. What you need is just a stretch hip. Built-in non-slip rubber strip,  classic colors and matching colors, it becomes fashionable and trendy in seconds.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ Convenient and Flexible - Easy to carry, you can use it anytime, anywhere. Train at home, at the gym or while traveling. Can be used for crossfit, yoga, Pilates, fitness. Lose weight or strengthen muscles.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ ENJOY FITNESS ANYTIME, ANYWHERE - The simple design of the resistance band allows you to enjoy fitness anywhere in the house without being affected by the environment. You only need one person to exercise. The resistance band is easy to install, easy to use. You can use a door frame and a door latch as a fitness aid at home.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ SUITABLE FOR EVERYONE - can help everyone – male or female, professional athlete or beginner. You can use the set for yoga, warming up before exercising, strength training or physical therapy rehabilitation.</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>LDLL</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>resistance bands fitness exercise loop workout pull up assist stretching strength training/conditioning physical therapy butt glute legs whole building gym training yoga pilates physiotherapy recovery non-slip skin-friendly coresteady set</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Exercise Bands</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>3407931</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <BedAndBath>
              <VariationData>
                <VariationTheme>Size</VariationTheme>
              </VariationData>
            </BedAndBath>
          </ProductType>
          <Parentage>parent</Parentage>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
</AmazonEnvelope>
