<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf8"?>
<AmazonEnvelope>
  <Header>
    <DocumentVersion>1.01</DocumentVersion>
    <MerchantIdentifier>AIEQD2KLS1F6W</MerchantIdentifier>
  </Header>
  <MessageType>Product</MessageType>
  <Message>
    <MessageID>1</MessageID>
    <OperationType>Update</OperationType>
    <Product>
      <SKU>ATRNA-571586482848</SKU>
      <StandardProductID>
        <Type>EAN</Type>
        <Value>9859476763398</Value>
      </StandardProductID>
      <DescriptionData>
        <Title>Pilates stick, Exercise Resistance Band Yoga Portable Fitness Bar Home Gym with Foot Loop Ideal for Physical Therapy, Strength Training, Muscle Toning</Title>
        <Brand>ATRNA</Brand>
        <Description><![CDATA[★ This controlled movement is not only great for building full-body athletic strength, it is also easy on joints and weak muscles that are recovering from overuse and injury. <br/>★ Welcome to ATRNA shop, thank your presence and trust! You can click on our shop to see more products.<br/>★ We will continue to update Resistance Band to provide customers with quality products.<br/><br/>★ Specification<br/>- Item Type: Resistance Band<br/>- Material: Natural latex tube / nylon / steel buckle<br/>- Color: Black-Red<br/><br/>★ Package List: <br/>- 1 * Resistance Band<br/><br/>★ Note<br/>- This product is only for sale of Resistance Band, other accessories are not included in the scope of sale, please pay attention when purchasing.<br/>- Because of the light effect and the different computer monitors, there may be the color difference.<br/>- Size is manual measurement, there will be 1-2cm error.<br/>- If you have any questions about these Pedal Resistance Band, please feel free to contact us and we will reply you email and solve your problem in 24h.]]></Description>
        <BulletPoint>★ CONVENIENT AND STURDY: The pole can be split and torn,the EVA feel comfortable,durable.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ ADJUSTABLE LENGTH: Adjustable buckle,quick length adjustment, quick and convenient.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ SAFE MATERIAL: Safe and anti-breaking design,sturdy imitation nylon structure.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ ANYTIME ANYWHERE: Home, hotel rooms, offices, and even outdoors Anytime, anywhere you want to start a sporting event or sport you want, it's very easy to carry and a small portable gym. Perfect home-based strength training.</BulletPoint>
        <BulletPoint>★ CUSTOMERS SERVICE: If you have any questions about these Resistance Band, please feel free to contact us and we will reply you email and solve your problem in 24h.</BulletPoint>
        <Manufacturer>ATRNA</Manufacturer>
        <SearchTerms>Pedal Resistance Band Tube Natural Latex Sit-up Bodybuilding Expander Elastic Pull Rope Fitness Equipment Abdomen Waist Arm Yoga Stretching Slimming Training Comfort Handles Exercise Portable Workouts Physical Therapy Strength Muscle Tension</SearchTerms>
        <ItemType>Strength Training Equipment</ItemType>
        <RecommendedBrowseNode>2438963011</RecommendedBrowseNode>
      </DescriptionData>
      <ProductData>
        <Home>
          <ProductType>
            <OutdoorLiving>
              <VariationData/>
            </OutdoorLiving>
          </ProductType>
        </Home>
      </ProductData>
    </Product>
  </Message>
</AmazonEnvelope>
